一！二！三！
One! Two! Three!
耶！
Yeah!
加油！耶！
Come on! Yeah!
加油！
Come on!
开始吧！加油！
Let's do this! Come on!
加油！
Come on!
加油！加油！
Come on! Come on!
来吧
Come on.
开始吧 加油
Let's do this. Come on.
下次大家站起来的时候 让背包滑下来
Let the backpack slip off next time everyone stands.
简在哪里？
Where's Jane?
丹尼尔·凯尔纳
Daniel Kellner.
你还想再见到她吗？
Do you want to see her again or not?
放松
Relax.
尽情享受比赛吧
Enjoy the match.
只需确认所有东西都在那里
Just got to make sure it's all there.
7.23.48.83
至 3.14.84A
through 3.14.84A.
11.17.55...
我总共制作了 107 个 IronClad 硬盘 每个 128 GB
I make a total of 107 IronClad drives, 128 gig each.
-你想让我重新计票吗？ -嗯 等我们做完之后 是的
-You want me to do a recount? -Uh, when we finish, yes.
打印文件约200页
Printed documents approximately 200 pages.
日期范围是什么？
What's the date range?
嗯 我们回去后可以把它编入目录
Uh, we can catalog that when we get back.
但我看到的最早可以追溯到 1947 年
But I'm seeing as far back as 1947
最近的可以追溯到去年
and as recent as last year.
唉 这一切都太令人失望了
Well, this is all rather disappointing.
简在哪里？
Where's Jane?
-你还好吗？ -是的
-Are you okay? -Yeah.
小心
Careful.
嘿
Hey.
是谁出卖了你？
Who turned you?
把所有人的名字都告诉我 你们俩可以叫辆出租车
Give me the names, all of them, and you two can call a cab.
它来了
It's here.
它在哪里？
Where is it?
把你的武器放在地上！
Put your weapon on the ground!
不要开火！不要开火
Do not fire! Do not fire.
如果开火 可能会激活该装置
If you fire, it could activate the device.
放松你的手 丹尼尔
Loosen your grip, Daniel.
用力挤压即可激活 请放松握力
If you squeeze, it activates. Soften your grip.
放下它 你不会用它
Put it down. You don't know how to use it.
-我知道你是怎么用的 -它差点要了我的命
-I know how you used it. -And it almost killed me.
现在 将设备放在地上
Now, place the device on the ground.
我应该以牙还牙 就像你对他们做的那样
I should do to you what you did to them.
塞雷娜 冷静下来
Stand down, Serena.
请勿对其施加任何压力
Do not exert any pressure on it.
放松你的手
Just loosen your grip.
放松你的手 就这样
Loosen your grip. That's it.
张开你的手
Just open your hand.
就是这样
That's it.
好的 好的
Okay. Okay.
把所有东西都塞进背包 然后上车
Sweep everything into the backpack and get in the car.
拜托 简
Please, Jane.
出去
Get out.
你没有运行任何恶意软件操作
You're not running some malware op.
在你的保密信息设施中 你不能躲在屏幕后面
You can't hide behind a screen in your SCIF.
世界正处于崩溃的边缘
The world is on the brink.
你真的认为倾销库存
Do you actually believe that dumping inventory
除了造成危险的干扰之外 不会有其他好处吗？
will be anything more than a dangerous distraction?
我旁听了审讯
I watched the interrogations.
历史记录没有重置键
History doesn't have a reset key.
如果你这样做 就无法挽回了
If you do this, there's no undoing it.
这就是计划
That's the plan.
博伊德
Boyd.
他坐在桌子旁
He sits at a desk.
他是怎么打败你的？
How did he beat you?
他们说你犯了叛国罪？
They said you committed treason?
这不是叛国罪 他们不是政府
It's not treason. They're not the government,
而且他们靠撒谎为生
and they lie for a living.
丹尼尔 到底发生了什么事？
What is going on, Daniel?
他们的车装有追踪器
Their cars have trackers.
我们必须摆脱它
We got to get rid of this.
请带我回家吧
Please just take me home.
他们会在你的公寓等你
They'd be waiting at your apartment.
嘿 把透明塑料袋递给我
Hey, hand me the clear plastic bag.
好的 稍微控制一下方向盘
Okay. Steer for a second.
好的 好的
Okay. Okay.
Okay, okay.
Hugo 我明白了
Hugo, I'm clear.
丹尼尔 我为你感到骄傲
Daniel, I'm so proud of you.
他们绑架了简 目的是为了找到我
They kidnapped Jane to get to me.
她现在和我在一起
She's with me now.
她没事吧？
Is she all right?
不完全是 雨果
Not really, Hugo.
我应该在哪里做drop？
Where do I do the drop?
尚未发布
No drop yet.
-确保安全 然后... -不 不 不
-Get secure, and then... -No, no, no.
现在就派人去把包拿过来
Send the guy for the bag now.
需要有人来负责这件事
Somebody needs to run with this thing.
那就是你
That's you.
你拿到球了
You've got the ball.
我不要球
I don't want the ball.
不 计划是我把它弄出设施 而且我做到了
No, the plan was I get it out of the facility, and I-I did.
我认为你是最有资格
I decided you were best qualified
保管这些材料的人
to keep the material safe.
你疯了吗？
Are you out of your mind?
不 我不是外勤人员 雨果
No, I'm not a field guy, Hugo.
技术工作是我做的 我只能做到这些
I-I did the tech work. That's all I can do.
你就待在我身边
You just stay with me.
我们按计划进行
We're on plan.
正在等待其他人被激活
Waiting now for someone else to be activated.
当他们出现时 我们就会知道接下来会发生什么
When they are, we'll know what comes next.
把简安置在安全的地方 然后安心过夜
Leave Jane somewhere safe and get secure for the night.
哦 不 我不会让她一个人待着的
Oh, no. I-I'm not leaving her alone.
-没有你 她会更安全 -但她并非如此
-She'll be safer without you. -But she wasn't.
安全的时候 你需要留下一个标记
I'm gonna need you to drop a marker when you get secure.
我们的朋友圣地亚哥明天早上会找到你
Our friend Santiago will find you in the morning.
我现在应该把所有东西都上传到网上
I should just dump everything online right now.
无论在任何情况下 你都不能这样做
You cannot, under any circumstances, do that.
现在 我们只能等待
For now, we wait.
保持警惕 寻找掩体
Stay alert. Find shelter.
圣地亚哥早上会把我们聚在一起
Santiago will put us together in the morning.
销毁你的手机
Destroy your phone.
丹尼
Danny.
卫星一次性手机
Satellite burner phones.
他们有自己的加密网络
They got their own encrypted network.
我们只使用一次
We only use them once.
你的职业具体是做什么的？
What exactly do you do for a living?
我们今晚得确保安全
We got to get secure for the night.
没有公寓 没有汽车旅馆
No apartments, no motels.
必须是我这辈子从未去过的地方
Has to be somewhere I've never been before in my life.
我知道附近有个地方
I know a place close to here.
国防部的马斯格雷夫想要听取简报
Musgrave at DoD wants a briefing.
立即把韦克菲尔德弄到这里来
Get Wakefield down here now.
告诉穆斯格雷夫 这只是一次轻微的违规行为
Tell Musgrave it was a minor breach.
恢复正在进行中
Recovery is in process.
先生 他不会想从我这里听到这些
Sir, he will not want to hear it from me.
如果我接电话 就表示我很担心
If I pick up the phone, it means I'm concerned.
如果他们哪怕闻到一丝风声 我们一个小时内就会把整个
If they even get a whiff of that, we'll have the entire
军事和情报机构都调到这里来
military and intelligence apparatus up here in an hour.
处理他
Handle him.
新闻推送里有相关的内容吗？
Anything relevant to this on news feeds?
尚未
Not yet.
社交账号还是安全私密账号？
Socials or secure private?
一片寂静
All quiet.
今天有12人未到场
12 no-shows here today.
所有办公桌都是空的
All with empty desks.
所有高于 G5 的间隙
All clearance above G5.
好的 所以我们正在处理一项
All right, so we're dealing with an operation
精心协调和执行的行动
carefully coordinated and executed.
为什么？目的是什么？
Why? With what goal?
如果他们想公开档案
If they wanted the archive out,
凯尔纳早就公开了
Kellner would have already released it,
但他没有公开 这意味着
but he hasn't, which means
有人在保留决策空间
somebody's maintaining decision space.
但是能持续多久 我们不知道 所以要尽快想办法
But for how long, we don't know, so think quickly.
Daniel Kellner 拥有
Daniel Kellner has a doctorate
理论和应用网络安全博士学位
in theoretical and applied cybersecurity,
并且他花了近八年时间
and he's spent the better part of eight years
保护高端数据
safeguarding high-side data,
这告诉我们关于他什么呢？
so what does that tell us about him?
想法
Ideas.
-来吧 -他建造了防火墙
-Come on. -He built the firewalls.
他知道如何突破它们
He knows how to breach them.
他们已经被攻破了 我们得克服这个难关
They're already breached. We got to play past that.
我们必须维持标准的跳跃追踪
We got to maintain standard skip tracing.
嗯 我可以访问 SYNTRAK
Well, I can access SYNTRAK.
他接下来会做什么？
What's the next thing he does?
先生
Sir.
Hugo Wakefield今天早上没来上班
Hugo Wakefield didn't show up for work this morning.
他的桌子被清空了
His desk was cleaned out.
雨果？
Hugo?
第二个设备在深度存储中缺失
Second device is missing from deep storage.
第三个在哪里？
Where's the third?
被锁在冷藏室里
Locked down in the cold room.
你怎么知道他们会回答？
How do you know they'll answer it?
因为这就是我们所做的
'Cause that's what we do.
你是怎么知道这个地方的？
How do you know this place?
简
Jane.
哦...哦 亲爱的
Oh... oh, my dear.
主教大人终于交出了他的运动鞋
The monsignor has finally surrendered his sneakers.
哦
Oh.
哦 我受不了他的其他鞋子
Oh, I couldn't bear his other shoes.
我知道 它们总是发出很刺耳的吱吱声
I know. They always squeaked so horribly.
哦 亲爱的 我们非常想念你
Oh, we have missed you very much, my dear.
哦 拜托
Oh, come on.
我所做的只是让你和其他姐妹们抓狂
All I ever did was drive you and the other sisters crazy.
嗯 你问的问题真多
Mm, well, you do ask a lot of questions.
特蕾莎最终完成她的见习期了吗？
Did Teresa ever get through her postulancy?
她顺利通过
She sailed through.
自从她不再晚上偷偷溜出去之后
Once she stopped sneaking out at night.
编号
No.
这位蒙席正在圣安东尼
The monsignor has her teaching
学校教三年级
third grade at St. Anthony's.
哦 她肯定很会和小朋友相处
Oh, she'll be fantastic with kids.
圣本笃
Saint Benedicta.
把它贴在你的眼睛上
Hold this against your eye.
我不会问你任何问题
I'm not going to ask you any questions.
这与我无关
It's not my business.
但简是
But Jane is.
无论你做了什么 你都必须为自己的行为负责
Whatever you have done, you must hold yourself accountable.
但别把简牵扯进来
But leave Jane out of it.
她可以和我们住在一起
She can stay with us.
你以前是修女吗？
You were a nun?
我们发生性关系了 你觉得怎么样？
We've had sex. What do you think?
我觉得你告诉我的关于你自己的所有事情都不是真的
I think everything you told me about yourself isn't true.
你真是胆大包天
You have an enormous amount of nerve.
是啊 我一直把事情藏在心里
Yeah, I kept things to myself
因为我签了卖身契 但你的事...
because I had to sign away my life, but your thing...
你真的是个修女？
You were an actual nun?
一名见习修士
A novitiate.
你为什么不说话？
Why didn't you say anything?
我省略了故事的一部分
I omitted a portion of my story.
人们会评判你
People judge you.
这一切是什么时候发生的？
When was all this?
三年前
Three years ago.
在你回答之前 我不会再回答任何问题
And I'm not answering any more questions until you do.
你偷了什么？
What did you steal?
我偷走了他们付钱让我保护的数据
I stole the data they paid me to protect.
你为什么要这样做？
Why would you do that?
因为人们有权知道真相
'Cause people have a right to know the truth.
你偷走的真相究竟是什么？
And what is it, this truth you stole?
所以...
So...
你想当修女 但是 你失去信仰了吗？
you wanted to be a nun, but what, you lost your faith?
我失去了我的使命感
I lost my calling.
你为这些人工作了多久？
How long have you worked for these people?
因为 嗯...
Since, um...
自从我八年
Since I got out...
前从联邦监狱出来...
of federal prison eight years ago.
我因网络犯罪在圣彼得堡服刑19个月
I did 19 months in Petersburg for cybercrimes.
WARDEX 在我出狱当天就直接从
WARDEX recruited me straight out of the parking lot
停车场招募了我
the day I was released.
-即使有犯罪记录？ -因为我的记录
-Even with your record? -Because of my record.
我靠保守秘密为生
I keep secrets for a living.
我不是故意瞒着你的
I-I didn't mean to keep them from you.
三个月前 我连现在所知道的一半都不知道
Three months ago, I didn't know half of what I know now.
简...
Jane...
我做的是对的
I'm doing the right thing.
我获取的数据并非专有数据
The data that I took, it's not proprietary.
不应该这样
It shouldn't be.
这是我们所知的真相
It's the truth we know.
WARDEX 并不拥有它 就像他们不能拥有
And WARDEX doesn't own it any more than they can own
空气或光一样
air or light.
我偷走的东西
What I stole,
它属于八十亿人
it belongs to eight billion people,
整个世界
the whole wide world.
我现在也是其中的一份子了
And I'm a part of it now.
我只是很抱歉...
I'm just sorry that...
他们也让你参与其中
that they made you a part of it, too.
你知道 所有那些温暖的
You know, and all that warm,
潮湿的空气一直徘徊着
moist air that's been hanging around,
它将与这股从北方
it is gonna smash into this cold front
呼啸而下的冷锋相撞
swooping down from the north.
它会将暖空气
It is gonna shove that warm air
一直推到对流层
all the way up through the troposphere.
它会疯狂地进行大规模压缩
It's gonna mass-condense it like crazy.
如果这种结构足够高
And if that formation goes high enough,
它会使水蒸气过冷
it'll supercool the water vapor.
我们将迎来我最喜欢的降雨
We're gonna get my favorite precipitation of all time.
米娅 我必须这么做 我必须这么做
Mia, I have to. I have to.
对不起 我做不到 我停不下来
I'm sorry, I can't. I can't stop.
下冰雹了
It's hail.
天气摇摆！
Weather Shimmy!
嘿！天气摇摆舞
Hey! The Weather Shimmy.
我们好久没看到这种举动了
We haven't seen that move in a while.
嗯 最近的天气实在没什么值得我
Well, the weather hasn't exactly given me
高兴的事情 你懂我的意思吗？
anything to dance about lately, you know what I mean?
我不知道我是否想要
I don't know if I want
令人兴奋的天气
exciting weather.
放松心情
Just let your hair down.
不 谢谢 我宁愿选择阳光明媚
No, thanks. I'll take a nice, boring 72 degrees
-气温宜人的72华氏度 -好吧 谢伊 你以后就别想再玩
-and sunny day anytime. -Fine, no more
天气摇摆舞了
Weather Shimmies for you, then, Shea.
-哦！ -就这样 不 结束了
-Oh! -That is it. Nope. Done.
无法将天气摇摆带走
Can't take Weather Shimmy away.
这是我最喜欢的东西
It's my favorite thing in the world.
嘿 你可以用这个掀起一股舞蹈热潮
Hey, you could start a dance craze with that.
你知道吗 我听说那些东西
You know, I hear there can be
里可以赚大钱
big money in those.
-我让你不要看那些 -太棒了
-Asked you not to watch those. -It's great.
-太棒了 -别这样
-It's great. -Don't even.
天气摇摆舞很热
The Weather Shimmy is hot.
-你打算留着它吗？ -是啊 你喜欢这样 是吗？
-You gonna keep it? -Yeah, you like that, huh?
我愿意 我愿意
I do. I do.
你知道吗？其他人也会这么想
You know what? So will everybody else.
这样说不会显得居高临下 因为我觉得
It wouldn't be so condescending, 'cause I think
你唯一真正搞错的就是天气
the only thing that you really got wrong was the weather.
我不知道 只是 呃...
I don't know, just, uh...
在我看来不像冰雹
doesn't look like hail to me.
你看了我发给你的东西吗？
Did you watch the thing I sent you?
什么？
What thing?
试镜
The audition.
哦 糟糕
Oh, shit.
是 不 对不起
Yes, no. I'm sorry.
对不起 我只是...我忘了
I'm sorry. I just... I forgot.
我现在就看
I'll watch it now.
好吧 但是听我说
Okay, but listen.
冈瑟帮我录下来了 好吗？
Gunther taped it for me, all right?
KCXE 的主播们自己编辑稿件
And the anchors edit their own copy at KCXE,
所以我自己写了稿子
so I wrote it myself.
-记住这一点 好吗？ -好的
-Just bear it in mind, okay? -Okay.
这里是堪萨斯城 KCXE 4 电视台的 Margaret Fairchild
This is Margaret Fairchild at KCXE 4 Kansas City.
平壤方面的报道出现了令人担忧的转折
Reports from Pyongyang took a worrying turn
朝鲜人民军异见分子又占领了四个军事基地
as KPA dissidents seized four more military bases
位于洛东江以东
east of the Nakdonggang River,
其中两个拥有核能力
including two with nuclear capability.
与此同时 俄罗斯国家电视台重申了
At the same time, Russian state television reiterated
迄今为止对首尔最严厉的威胁
its starkest threats yet to Seoul,
关于其在三八线集结兵力
regarding the massing of its forces at the 38th parallel.
在北方 副元帅朴明顺
In the North, Vice Marshal Pak Myong-sun
现在声称至少完全控制了...
now claims full control of at least...
很好
It's good.
很好 真的很好
It's good. That's really good.
-你真的...太好了 -真的吗？
-You're really... It's so good. -Really?
是啊 真的很好
Yeah, it's really good.
你...你...你很好
You're-you're... you're good.
你一直都很棒 我是认真的
You're always good. I'm serious.
听着 我就是很喜欢你现在正在做的事情
Look, it's just, I love what you're doing now.
你知道吗？你拥有天气控制能力
You know? You got weather power.
你顶着KCXE天气预报员的发型
You got KCXE weather hair on,
你知道 就像“K Sexy”
and, you know, it's like, "K Sexy."
我觉得我们应该搬家
I think we should move.
又来了？
Again?
-是的 -好的 你刚刚给租来的阁楼卧室贴好了壁纸
-Yep. -Okay. You just wallpapered
现在你想再动一下
the bedroom in a rented loft, and you want to move again.
-我知道 -你现在想搬到哪里？
-I know. -Where-where do you want to move now?
我不知道 就是 比如 更大的市场 更大的城市
I don't know, just, like, bigger market, bigger city.
我们去年在达拉斯
We were in Dallas last year.
-那不是更大的市场吗？ -达拉斯是...
-That's not a bigger market? -Dallas is...
达拉斯感觉不对劲 不对劲...
Dallas didn't feel right, didn't...
我不知道 我只是觉得
I don't know, I just don't think
达拉斯不是我应该待的地方
Dallas is where I was supposed to be.
好吧 那么...好吧 Maggie 你现在应该在哪里？
Well, then... okay, like, where are you supposed to be, Maggie?
到了那里我就知道了
I'm gonna know when I get there.
我是
I am.
蜂蜜
Honey.
你就不能安静地坐一会儿吗？
Can't you just sit still for, like, one minute?
好的
Okay.
看
Look.
-我在这里很好 -我知道
-I'm good here. -I know.
好吗？感觉我状态正佳
Okay? Like, I'm in the flow.
我可以播放自己的歌了 我不用再当DJ了
I get to play my own stuff. I don't have to DJ anymore.
我刚刚在 McFeely's 找到了周三和周六的工作
I just got Wednesdays and Saturdays down at McFeely's.
解决所有问题的办法并非只是把东西打包搬到U-Haul货车上
The answer to every problem is not just to pack up the U-Haul.
看 看 看
Look, look, look.
哇
Wow.
哦...哦 我的天哪
Oh... oh, my God.
太疯狂了
That's crazy.
好了 走吧 快走 离开这里
All right, go. Shoo. Get out of here.
走 快走 离开这里
Go. Shoo. Out of here.
真是只胆大的小鸟啊！
Gutsy little bird, huh?
Mag 你还好吗？
Mag, you okay?
嘿 Mag 你还好吗？你还好吗？
Hey, Mag, you okay? You okay?
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
-呃... -纽约...
-Uh... -New York...
芝加哥
...Chicago.
你在哪里学到的...
Where did you learn...
Mag
Mag.
好的
Okay.
好的 哇 好的 玛吉
All right, wow. Okay, Maggie.
好了 停 停 停 停
Okay, stop, stop, stop, stop.
好了 停
Okay, stop.
住手！住手！
Stop it! Stop!
那到底是什么鬼东西？
What the hell was that?
你是什么意思？
What do you mean?
是俄语 还是波兰语或其他什么语言？
Is it Russian, or is it Polish or something
-比如 讲个故事？ -亲爱的 我没关注你
-for, like, a story? -I'm not following you, sweetie.
你昨天学的就是这个吗...
Was that what you were learning yester...
什么意思？我们只是在讨论而已
What do you mean? We're just talking about it.
你什么时候学会俄语的？
Wh-When did you learn Russian?
俄语？
Russian?
我不知道
I don't know.
哦 天哪 我得走了 我迟到了
Ooh. Oh, God, I got to go. I'm late.
我7点23分开始直播 我的直播时间提前了
I'm on live at 7:23. I got moved up.
-哦 好的 -好的
-Oh. Okay. -Okay.
我们待会儿再说吧 好吗？我得穿鞋
Let's just talk about it later, okay? I need my shoes.
嗯 我们现在可以谈谈这件事了...
Well, uh, we can talk about it now and...
-我的天哪 我的天哪 我的天哪 -喜欢 如果你...
-Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. -Like, if you...
-如果你想拿你的钱包 就在这里 -哦 嗯！
-if you want to get your purse, here. -Oh. Mm!
-没关系 一切都好 -是的
-It's okay. It's all okay. -Yeah.
我们可以...我们可以讨论一下 好吗？
We can... we can discuss it, okay?
-好的 是的 -我爱你
-Okay, yeah. -I love you.
我也爱你
Love you, too.
-再见 -好的
-Bye. -Okay.
♪ 呜呼 耶呼 ♪
♪ Woo-hoo, yee-hoo ♪
♪ 呜呼 ♪
♪ Woo-hoo ♪
♪ 耶呼 ♪
♪ Yee-hoo ♪
♪ 呜呼 耶呼 ♪
♪ Woo-hoo, yee-hoo ♪
♪ 呜呼 ♪
♪ Woo-hoo ♪
-♪ 耶呼 ♪ -♪ 如果我能逃脱 ♪
-♪ Yee-hoo ♪ -♪ If I could escape ♪
♪ 我会的 但首先 让我说 ♪
♪ I would, but first of all, let me say ♪
♪ 我必须为我糟糕的行为道歉 ♪
♪ I must apologize for acting stank ♪
♪ 以及我这样对待你 因为我一直表现得像 ♪
♪ And treating you this way, 'cause I've been acting like ♪
♪ 酸奶洒了一地 ♪
♪ Sour milk all on the floor ♪
♪ 都是你的错 你没关冰箱门... ♪
♪ It's your fault, you didn't shut the refrigerator... ♪
哦 糟糕
Oh, shoot.
♪ 如果我能逃离 ♪
♪ If I could escape ♪
♪ 并重建一个属于我自己的世界... ♪
♪ And re-create a place that's my own world... ♪
对不起 别怪我 要怪就怪音乐吧 我真的很抱歉
Sorry, don't blame me. Blame the music. I'm so sorry.
请把引擎关掉
Go ahead and turn your engine off for me, please.
当然 是的 你知道的 就像 这是一首欢快的歌
Sure, yeah. You know how it is. Like, it's a fun song,
今天天气真好 你就跟着唱
it's a beautiful day, you just sing along,
你唱得太快了 然后...
you go too fast and...
驾照和登记
License and registration.
绝对的
Absolutely.
就是这样
Here's that.
这里是...
Here's...
就是这样
There you go.
请从钱包里拿出您的驾照
Go ahead and take your license out of your wallet, please.
当然 是的
Sure. Yeah.
这是一张老照片
It's an old picture.
请您下车吧
Just go ahead and step out of the car, please.
嗯 这...这真的有必要吗？
Um, is... is that totally necessary?
只是 因为我的工作 我必须
It's just, for my job, I have to be
一分不差 精确到分钟
exactly on the dot, like, to the minute,
-因为我们还要继续... -我明白了
-'cause we go on... -I get it.
我知道你是谁 天气可以等等
I know who you are. The weather can wait.
请你下车一会儿
Just step out of the car for me, please.
先生 我...
Sir, I...
我不想再问你一遍了
I don't want to have to ask you again.
哦 你今天心情不好
Oh, you're just having a bad day.
什么？
What?
-她不是那个意思 -谁？
-She didn't mean it. -Who?
安娜 她今天早上对你说的那些话
Anna. Those things she said to you this morning,
她不是那个意思 她不是那个意思
she didn't mean it, she didn't mean it.
就这么自然而然地说出来了 这很难
It just kind of came out. It's hard.
她整夜都在照顾宝宝
She's up all night with the baby.
你怎么知道...
How do you know...
去给她买红丝绒纸杯蛋糕
Go get her the red velvet cupcakes.
这是个好主意...上面撒上紫色糖屑
It's a good idea-- with the purple sprinkles on them.
然后今晚你去海王星餐桌
And then tonight you go to Neptune's Table,
你点了龙虾
you order the lobster,
你用龙虾钳做了那个滑稽的动作
you do that funny thing with the claws.
这总能逗她笑 很好 很好
That always makes her laugh. It's good, it's good.
你不后悔生了这个孩子
You don't regret having the baby.
你爸跟谁都不一样 别再这么自欺欺人了
Nothing like your dad. Stop telling yourself that.
你知道那张上面有跳舞天使的卡片吗？
You know the card with the dancing angels on it?
真好 真漂亮
It's nice. It's beautiful.
千万别在里面写长篇道歉信
Just don't go writing the big apology inside.
她不需要 她只需要睡个午觉
She doesn't need it. She just needs a nap.
她需要睡个午觉 你也应该睡一会儿
She needs a nap, and you could do with one, too.
你觉得我现在可以走了吗？
Do you think I could go now?
谢谢
Thank you.
这他妈什么鬼...
What the fu...
全球紧张局势接近临界点
Global tensions are near a breaking point
据报道 美国和俄罗斯的战略轰炸机
as both American and Russian strategic bombers
已飞往其故障安全点
have reportedly flown to their fail-safe points,
随时准备执行打击命令
ready to proceed with strike orders if given.
五角大楼罕见地发表公开声明 确认
In a rare public statement, the Pentagon confirmed
美国已将其国防战备状态提升至
that the United States has raised
DEFCON 2
its defense readiness condition to DEFCON 2.
苏珊·拉米雷斯上校今天早些时候发表了一份措辞严厉的信息：
Colonel Susan Ramirez issued a stark message earlier today:
“我们正处于国家自1962年古巴导弹危机
"We are in the most dangerous hours our nation has faced
以来最危险的时刻...”
since the 1962 Cuban Missile..."
哦 上帝
Oh, God.
-你真的迟到了 -我知道 我知道
-You're really late. -I know. I know.
这不是我的错
It's not my fault.
在家乡
Here at home, there's been
大量居民逃离了靠近重要军事设施的地区
a surge of residents fleeing areas
包括...
near key military installations, including...
-克莱 我知道 不 -哇 你真慷慨
-Clay. I know. No. -Wow. Very generous of you
竟然在直播开始前三分钟就到了
to show up three minutes before you're on.
这是无法避免的 这个警察...
It could not be avoided. This cop...
不 你知道什么无法避免吗？
No, you know what can't be avoided?
-把我拦了下来 -截止日期
-...pulled me over. -Deadlines.
我知道 我明白 我很抱歉
I know. I understand. I'm so sorry.
如果我们说 “现在请玛格丽特·费尔柴尔德为您播报天气...”
If we say, "Now here's Margaret Fairchild with the weather..."
-右 -然后镜头切到你 却发现你不在
-Right. -...and we cut to you and there's no you,
-这就是截稿日期的问题 -彻底的灾难 简直
-that's the deadline problem. -Total disaster. It's just,
-我刚刚遇到了一件非常奇怪的事情 -我能...
-the weirdest thing just happened to me. -Can I just...
-我需要... -向上 向上 向上
-I need to... -Up, up, up.
咱们边跑边做吧 走吧
Let's do it on the run. Come on.
-动起来 动起来 动起来 动起来 动起来 -好的 好的 把我的鞋子还给我
-Move, move, move, move, move. -Okay. Okay, give me my shoes.
-我们正处于危机模式 -好的
-We're in crisis mode. -Okay.
您的片段被剪辑至90秒
Your segment's cut to 90 seconds.
然后你把镜头转向谢伊 让他谈谈州长的“保持冷静”那件事
Then you throw to Shea for the governor's "remain calm" thing.
-嗯 -然后网络提前将其收回
-Mm-hmm. -Then network takes it back early.
这个警察把我拦了下来 我甚至不知道发生了什么事
This cop pulled me over, and I don't even know what happened.
我就开始说话了
I just started talking,
话就说了出来 我就想...
and the words were just coming out, and I was just like...
嗯 休息的时候告诉我
Yeah, tell me at the break.
-但是 他好像明白这意味着什么 -不 不 你知道吗？
-But, like, he knew what it meant. -No, no, you know what?
-告诉我永远不会 -好的
-Tell me never. -Okay.
如果你有一天想
And if someday you want to even
有机会成为周末主播
be considered for weekend anchor,
-就别再这样对我了 -别这么说
-don't do this to me again. -Don't say that.
-那是谁？ -朴大成
-Who is that? -DaeSeong Park.
密歇根大学韩国研究所访问学者
Visiting fellow at the Korean Studies Institute at U of M.
-哦 天哪 他为什么这么生气？ -因为他是韩国人
-Oh, gosh, why is he so upset? -'Cause he's Korean.
你什么都没听懂吗？90秒
Are you not following anything? 90 seconds.
玛格丽特 来吧 这边走
Margaret, come on. This way.
你该去报警了
It's time for you to go to the police.
必须有人阻止他 玛丽亚需要你
Someone has to stop him. Maria needs you.
现在就做 现在就做
Do it now. Do it now.
他的意思是说朝鲜的行为
He's saying that the actions
是可以理解的 而且...
of North Korea are understandable and...
不 不 不好意思
No, no. Excuse me.
不 不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no. No.
“似曾相识 ”“似曾相识 ”他说
"Recognizable." "Recognizable," he said.
-可预测 -可预测 是啊
-Predictable. -Predictable. Yeah.
是的 他的意思是...
Yes. He's saying...
不 他的意思是这些行为是不正当的
No, he's saying the actions are not justified.
它们只是似曾相识而已 事态正在升级
They're only familiar. There's this escalation.
这遵循某种模式 你知道 这遵循某种模式
It follows a pattern. You know, it follows a pattern.
这不是 嗯...他不是在支持侵略行为
It's not, um... he's not endorsing aggression.
这是一个非常重要的区别
It's a very important distinction.
抱歉 这些词的意思有点接近
Sorry, the words are just kind of close.
没关系 我想你只是没听到他说话
It's okay. I think you just didn't hear him.
你什么时候开始会说韩语的？
Since when do you speak Korean?
会说韩语？什么？
Speak Korean? What?
看在上帝的份上 你还有15分钟就上场了
For God's sake, you're on in 15.
好的 我知道 我知道 我知道
Okay. I know, I know, I know.
来自西北方向的停滞锋面将于下午中旬穿过
Stalled front from the northwest is gonna move through
-大都会区 -嗯哼
-metro area midafternoon. -Uh-huh.
气温骤降 暴雨 可能伴有冰雹
Rapid temp drops, heavy rain, maybe hail.
注意天气等等
Stay weather-aware, et cetera, et cetera.
-五秒钟 -全部加载完毕
-Five seconds. -It's all loaded in.
让我们请玛格丽特·费尔柴尔德来播报天气预报
Let's go to Margaret Fairchild with the forecast,
她会告诉我们今天会发生什么
and she'll tell us what's in store for us today.
-玛格丽特 -谢谢你 米娅
-Margaret. -Thanks, Mia.
早上好 堪萨斯城
And good morning, Kansas City.
让我们来看看今天...
Let's take a look at today...
让我们...让我们...让我们来看看今天的情况
Let's... let's... let's take a look at today.
我们要...我们要看看今天 今天...
W-We're gonna... we're gonna take a look at today. Today...
今天是...
today is...
今天是...今天...
T-T-Today is... today...
今天是...
T-Today is...
放开她
Get off her.
-放开她 镜头切走 -好的 把它转到三号摄像机那里
-Get off her. Cut away. -Okay. Take it to camera three.
把镜头对准三号机位 去 你得拍下来 拍下来
Take it to camera three. Go. You got to take it. Take it.
好的 显然地图
Okay. Clearly some troubles with the maps
以及天气预报和我们的声音都有些问题
and the, uh, forecast and our sound.
让我们来处理这件事 因为我们知道
Let us work on that, because we know
您今天早上需要天气预报
you need your weather news this morning.
我们稍作休息
We'll take a short break,
回来后 我们会看看你明天是否需要带上
and when we come back, we'll find out if you need to take
你的雨伞或防晒霜
your umbrella or your sunscreen with you tomorrow.
与我们同在
Stay with us.
-哇 哇 哇 -玛格丽特
-Whoa, whoa, whoa. -Margaret.
-玛格丽特 玛格丽特！ -叫救护车！
-Margaret. Margaret! -Call an ambulance!
-喝点水 -嘿 嘿 嘿！
-Get some water. -Hey, hey, hey!
-玛格丽特！ -玛格丽特！
-Margaret! -Margaret!
所有人 请后退！
Everybody, back up, please!
哦 糟糕
Oh, shit.
你在这里很安全
You're safe here.
一旦我摆脱了这件事 我就会回来
Soon as I'm out from under this, I'm coming back.
我向你保证 我一定会回来找你的
I promise you, I am coming back for you.
是吗？
Yeah?
是的
Yeah.
今天真是个睡懒觉的好日子 你知道吗？
Hell of a day to sleep in, you know that?
对不起 对不起
Sorry. Sorry.
回到里面
Get back inside.
这是你能待的最安全的地方
This is the safest place you can be.
不久之后 我会说
At some point soon, I'll say,
“丹尼 是时候把一切都告诉我了”
"Danny, it's time you tell me everything."
你会把一切都告诉我
And you will tell me everything.
我们还在等什么？
What are we waiting for?
走吧
Let's go.
雨果 我们现在该怎么办？
Hugo, what do we do now?
我必须保留这个多久？
How long do I have to hold on to this?
把您交给圣地亚哥 您就放心吧
You're in good hands with Santiago.
他很清楚他要带你去哪里
He knows exactly where he's taking you.
向下！
Down!
WARDEX 清除
WARDEX. Clear.
他们正在外面找我
They're out here looking for me.
我该如何才能让我们活下去？
How am I supposed to keep us alive?
圣地亚哥正带你去安全屋
Santiago is taking you to a safe house.
到达后 您可以再来找我办理入住手续
When you arrive, you can check back in with me.
多布斯将军 您已经了解了
General Dobbs, you have learned
我们所知道的事情
what we know when we know it,
远远超出了我们的报告义务
far in excess of our reporting obligations.
让我们来做个方位角检查
Let-let's get an Azimuth Check here.
这是贵组织历史上最
This is the most significant security lapse
-严重的安全漏洞 -这是一场灾难
-in your organization's history. -It's a catastrophe.
国防部拥有大量可立即部署的IRR
DoD has significant IRR that we can deploy immediately.
这是个错误 不要打开这个光圈
That is a mistake. Do not open the aperture on this.
-运营重叠... -我们有12,000名FBI外勤特工
-Operational overlap... -There are 12,000 FBI field agents
-可供我们使用 -真是个糟糕的主意！
-at our disposal. -...is a terrible idea!
我不知道为什么我们不利用它们
I don't know why we don't utilize them.
我们最不需要的就是12000名信息不足的联邦人员
The last thing we need is 12,000 underinformed Feds
到处招摇撞骗 引人注目
stomping around and calling attention to themselves,
所以请各司其职
so please stay in your lane.
如果我们需要完整的战斗计划 我会打电话给你
If we need the full battle rattle, I'll call you.
抱歉打断一下
Sorry to interrupt.
这条消息刚刚在社交媒体上疯传
This just hit social media.
来自密苏里州堪萨斯城的电视新闻广播
A TV news broadcast from Kansas City, Missouri.
它现在已经发布了
It's out there now.
她是谁？
Who is she?
堪萨斯城 KCXE 4 电视台当地天气预报员
Local weather lady at KCXE 4, Kansas City, Missouri.
玛格丽特·费尔柴尔德 38岁
Margaret Fairchild, 38,
出生于加利福尼亚州塞里托斯 未婚 无子女
born Cerritos, California, never married, no children,
拥有广播学士学位
bachelor's degree in broadcasting.
我们的档案里有方言样本吗？
Do we have a dialect sample in the archives?
是
Yes.
而且匹配成功
And it matched.
-你想做什么？ -在雨果找到她之前找到她
-What do you want to do? -Find her before Hugo does.
我们在堪萨斯城有哪些工作人员？
Who do we have on the ground in Kansas City?
我正在处理
I'm on it.
好的 玛格丽特 我们开始吧
Okay, Margaret, we're gonna get started.
考试会很吵闹
Test is gonna be really noisy,
所以我把这个球给你
so I'm gonna give you this ball in your hand
以防你在考试过程中需要我
in case if you need me throughout the test.
需要停止的时候就捏它 好吗？
Squeeze it any time you need to stop, okay?
-好的 是的 -闭上眼睛 好吗？
-Okay, yeah. -Keep your eyes closed, okay?
在你待在里面的这段时间里 我会一直跟你说话
I'll be speaking to you the entire time
-好吗？ -好的
-you're in there, okay? -Okay.
好了 开始了 你要进去了
And here we go. You're going in.
-你好吗？ -我很好
-How are you doing? -I'm fine.
哦 看
Oh, look.
看 看 看
Look, look, look.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
它们只是鹿而已
They're just deer.
就是那种眼神
It's that stare.
就像...
It's like...
就像他们很害怕 但其实他们并不害怕
It's like they're scared, but they're not.
它们很大胆
They're bold,
但当你伸手去拿相机时 它们就跑了
but they run when you reach for your camera.
丹尼 时候到了
It's time, Danny.
发生了什么事？
What is going on?
就算我说出来 你也不会相信
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
所以我要给你们展示一下
So I'm gonna show you.
您的核磁共振结果正常
Your MRI is normal.
无中风或肿块
No strokes or masses.
所以 它不是肿瘤 也没有梗死
So, it's not neoplastic, and there's no infarction.
你什么都没找到吗？
You didn't find anything?
大多数人都会觉得这令人安心
Most people would find that reassuring.
嗯 我只是...我这是怎么了？
Well, I just... What's going on with me?
这根本说不通
That just doesn't make sense.
你最近压力很大吗？
Well, have you been under a lot of stress lately?
否 否
No. No.
我的意思是 今天 但不是今天之前
I mean, today, but not before today.
你父亲患有帕金森病吗？
Your father had Parkinson's?
你是说就是这样吗？
Are you saying that's what it is?
不 不 不 不一定
No, no, no. Not necessarily.
但发病年龄是多少？
But at what age was onset?
他46岁 47岁
He was 46, 47.
他去世时我还是个十几岁的孩子 而且...
I was a teenager when he died, and...
他们在监视我们吗？那些人是谁？
Are they watching us? Who are those guys?
他们是联邦调查局的人
They're with the FBI.
我们这里结束后 他们还有一些问题要问你
They have some questions for you after we're finished here.
你怎么知道他们是FBI？
How do you know they're FBI?
他们出示了身份证明
They showed identification.
他们不是FBI
They're not FBI.
费尔柴尔
Ms. Fairchild...
德女士...您是否曾就童年时期发生的
have you ever sought counseling for the traumatic event
创伤事件寻求过心理咨询？
that happened when you were a child?
我不记得了 我当时十岁
I don't remember it. I was ten years old.
你是否做过与该事件相关的噩梦？
Do you have nightmares related to the event?
编号
No.
一直如此 一直如此
A-All the time. All the time.
嗯 还是那个关于蝴蝶的梦
Uh, it's the same dream about butterflies
和森林里的“汉塞尔与格雷特”小屋
and a "Hansel and Gretel" house in the woods.
嗯 而且 她有时还会梦游唱歌
Um, and also, she sings in her sleep sometimes.
-不 我不那样做 -小孩子的歌曲
-No, I don't do that. -Little kids' songs.
-我不那样做 我会那样做吗？ -你做到了 你做到了 你做到了
-I don't do that. Do I do that? -You do. You do. You do.
她确实会
She does.
-请稍等片刻 -你在做什么？
-Excuse me a minute. -What are you doing?
-她需要信息...什么？ -你怎么能这样做...
-She needs the infor... What? -How could you do...
-他们需要这些信息 -你怎么能告诉他们
-They need the information. -How could you tell them
我除了你以外从未告诉过任何人的那件事？
the one thing I never told anyone but you?
你没跟我详细说 我不知道
You didn't tell me much about it. I don't know.
因为我不记得了 然后你告诉
Because I don't remember it, and then you tell
一个完全陌生的人 说我会在睡梦中唱歌
a complete stranger that I sing in my sleep.
我的意思是 我睡觉的时候也会说韩语吗？
I mean, do I speak Korean in my sleep, too?
他们不是陌生人 他们是医生
They're not strangers. They're doctors.
你在他们面前脱下裤子
You pull your pants down in front of them.
你告诉他们一些事情 就是这样
You tell them stuff. That's how it works.
FBI到底在这里干什么？
What the hell is the FBI doing here?
凯尔纳 丹尼尔·凯尔纳
Kellner. Daniel Kellner.
丹尼尔·凯尔纳
Daniel Kellner.
-呃... -你知道他是谁吗？
-Uh... -Do you know who that is?
呃 嗯 那是科尔曼博士
Uh, um, that's Dr. Coleman.
丹尼尔·凯尔纳是谁？
Who's Daniel Kellner?
我不知道 但那些家伙希望他死了
I don't know, but those guys wish he was dead.
什么？
What?
装作我需要帮助才能去洗手间
Act like I need help getting to the bathroom.
-好的？ -你呢？
-Okay? -Do you?
杰克逊 你就不能顺其自然吗？我的天哪
Can you just roll with it, Jackson? My God.
好的 稍等 是的
All right, hang on. Yeah.
嗨 呃 她想去趟洗手间
Hi. Uh, she needs to use the bathroom.
-我只是想去趟洗手间 -是的
-I just need the bathroom. -Yeah.
-好的 很好 -好的？好的？
-Okay. Good. -Okay? Okay?
好的 很好 好的
Okay. Good. Okay.
好的 我们 嗯...
All right, let's, um...
我们能稍微谈谈吗？
Just, can we talk about it for a second?
-呃 嘿 Mag 我们能谈谈吗？ -哦 完美
-Uh, hey, Mag, can we talk? -Oh, perfect.
好了 我们能慢下来一分钟吗？
All right, can we just slow down for one minute?
我只是想 呃 和你谈谈你在做什么
I just want to, uh, talk to you about what you're doing.
Maggie Maggie Maggie
Maggie, Maggie, Maggie.
-Maggie 你在做什么？ -穿衣服
-Maggie, what are you doing? -Getting dressed.
-我们要走了 我们要走了 -什么？
-We're leaving. We're leaving. -What?
-我得走了 我得走了 -什么？
-Got to go. Got to go. -What?
-我得走了 -你在说什么...
-Got to go. -What are you talk...
-哦 天哪 我太抱歉了 -嗨 呃...
-Oh, God. I'm so sorry. -Hi. Uh...
-打扰一下 -你是什么意思？
-Excuse me. -What do you mean?
-你是说逃出去吗？ -是的
-You mean busting out? -Yep.
-你...你怎么了？ -问题是我有一个
-Wh-What's wrong with you? -What's wrong is I have
非常不配合的男朋友 对吧...
a very uncooperative boyfriend right...
-哦 你一定是在开玩笑吧 -什么？我做了什么？
-Oh, you got to be kidding me. -What? What did I do?
你完全明白我在说什么
You know exactly what I'm talking about.
我做了什么？玛吉
What did I do? Maggie.
鞋子 鞋子 鞋子
Shoes. Shoes, shoes.
是啊 当然
Yeah, sure.
-这里 -谢谢
-Here. -Thank you.
你好吗？
How's it going?
WARDEX？
WARDEX?
代表豁免报告开发和提取
Stands for Waived Reporting Development and Extraction.
什么？
Of what?
佛罗里达州霍姆斯特德空军基地 1973 年
Homestead Air Force Base in Florida, 1973.
和尼克松在一起的那个人是谁？
Who's the guy with Nixon?
50年代的大电视明星
Big TV star in the '50s.
尼克松想给他留下深刻印象
Nixon wanted to impress him.
他们是孩子吗？
Are they children?
编号
No.
他们是...人吗？
Are they... people?
编号
No.
他们是人类吗？
Are they human?
接下来的部分令人难以观看
This next part's hard to watch.
是雨果向我展示的东西让我入了坑
It's what Hugo showed me that got me into this.
好的？
Okay?
好的
Okay.
我们需要生命体征
We're gonna need vitals.
我们没有基线
We've got no baseline.
脉搏血氧仪无法读取
Pulse ox can't read.
-没有标准地标... -氯胺酮？
-No standard landmarks... -Ketamine?
-四到六毫克？ -不再使用镇静剂
-Four to six milligrams? -No more sedatives.
我首先需要基线压力数据
I want baseline stress data first.
调整握法 固定脚踝
Shift your grip. Secure the ankles.
稳定头部和右臂
Stabilize head and right arm.
头部晃动幅度过大
Head's moving too much.
我需要一个带衬垫的约束带
I need a padded restraint.
我有了 我需要脑脊液
I have it. I need cerebrospinal fluid.
将针推进18厘米
Advance the needle 18 centimeters,
延髓腹侧
ventral to the medulla.
它情况危急 正在注射丙泊酚
It's in distress. Administering propofol.
阴性 未麻醉
Negative. No anesthesia.
我们那样丢了一个 现在就做
We lost one that way. Do it now.
立即插入
Insert it now.
还有更多
There's more.
79 年
79 years more.
我全都有
I have all of it.
只有雨果与它有关系
Hugo is the only one who had a relationship with it,
而且他知道自己在用那东西做什么
and he knew what he was doing with that thing.
调出凯尔纳的数据
Pull up Kellner's data.
把设备给我
Give me the device.
如果收缩压低于90
If systolic goes below 90
像上次那样 我就把你拉出来
like last time, I'm pulling you out.
注意快速性心律失常
Watch for tachyarrhythmia,
-硬膜下出血 -复制
-subdural hemorrhage. -Copy.
我没事 我没事！
I'm fine. I'm fine!
发生了什么事？
What happened?
我全神贯注 全身心投入
I had focus, gave myself over,
瞥见凯尔纳一瞬间 然后...
saw Kellner for a split second, then...
大锤 一片空白
sledgehammer, whiteout.
把我的肺里的空气都抽走了
Sucked all the air out of my lungs.
他是体验者吗？
Is he an experiencer?
你不能跳到它们上面
You can't dive on them.
他不可能在那里 如果是的话 我肯定会知道
He can't have been. I'd have known.
他是雨果的人
He's Hugo's guy.
还有很多我们不知道的事情
There's gonna be a whole lot we don't know.
也许吧 但我不会再进去一探究竟
Maybe, but I'm not going back in there to find out.
获取女朋友的数据
Pull the data on the girlfriend.
曾有过一些异域飞行器的回收计划
There have been retrieval programs of exotic craft.
对非人类生物制品的审讯
Interrogation of nonhuman biologics.
逆向工程和技术利用
Reverse engineering and technology exploitation.
所有这一切...
All of it...
由 WARDEX 国防部
run by WARDEX, the Department of Defense
和国防工业运营
and the defense industry.
它拥有美国历史上最高的军事
It has the highest level of military
和私营部门分类
and private sector classification
级别
in American history.
他们从 70 年代初就开始运营它
They've run it since the early '70s
没有政府资助
without government funding.
太多的税款需要隐藏
Too many tax dollars to try and hide,
而且外星文物利润太高
and-and off-world artifacts are too profitable
不能交给指定的官员
to leave in the hands of appointed officials,
尤其是在尼克松事件之后
especially after the Nixon thing.
总统在八年后又变回了平民 所以...
Presidents are civilians again after eight years, so...
所以没有理由再让他们了解这一切了
so there's no longer a reason to read them in on any of this.
我曾经也是这一切的一部分 直到我看到了你刚才看到的东西
I was a part of all that until I saw what you just saw.
这一切到此结束
This all stops now.
你打算怎么办？
What are you gonna do?
一次性向全世界完全公开
Full disclosure to the whole world all at once.
你考虑过这会造成什么影响吗？
Have you considered what effect that'll have?
所有东西？
On everything?
什么...
What...
这并非由我决定...
It's not up to me to decide if it's...
这究竟是好是坏 还是应该让别人知道
if it's good or bad for people to know.
那么 凭什么由你来决定知情权
Then how is it up to you to decide that the right to know
是否大于知情的后果呢？
outweighs the consequences of knowing?
你是说我们要把这件事交给WARDEX来处理吗？
Are you saying we leave this up to WARDEX?
因为他们...他们已经决定这属于他们
'Cause they-they've already decided this belongs to them,
关于宇宙的核心真理
this core truth about the universe.
-这是错误的 -你不能这样做
-It's wrong. -You can't do that.
想想...
Think about...
人们会将他们视为神明
People will see them as deities.
他们将不再信仰上帝
They'll stop believing in God.
好吧 你离开了教会
Well, you left the church.
不是因为我不再相信
Not because I stopped believing,
因为我不能再肯定地说
because I could no longer say with certainty
上帝是神圣的
that God is divine,
但我深信他是必不可少的
but I believe profoundly that he's essential.
他就是我们对自己的定义
He's how we define ourselves.
他是维系整个文明的关键
He's what keeps whole civilizations together.
我们从小就被灌输信仰至高无上的神灵
We've been raised to believe in a supreme being,
现在你们想向我们展示真正的至高无上的神灵？
and now you want to show us actual supreme beings?
人们无法同时兼顾两者
People can't handle both.
当然可以
Of course they can.
不 他们不能
No, they can't.
回顾我们历史上的任何突发变化
Look at our history with any sudden change.
现在 世界即将在我们所有人面前爆炸？
And now, with the world about to blow up in all our faces?
你会陷入恐慌和混乱 上帝保佑我们
You'll get panic and-and chaos, and God help us.
Hugo 等着我报到
Hugo's expecting me to check in.
无信号
No signal.
我试试山坡的另一边
I'll try the other side of the hill.
好的
Okay.
打开门！
Unlock the door!
-什么？ -杰克逊 加油！
-What? -Jackson, come on!
哦 糟糕 对不起
Oh, shit. Sorry.
哦 对不起 对不起
Oh, sorry, sorry.
-好的 -我的天哪
-Okay. -Oh, my God.
如果你用法语回答这个问题 我向上帝发誓
If you answer that in French, I swear to God
我会把你押回里面
I'm marching you right back inside.
你好？
Hello?
我等了很久
I've been waiting a very long time
才见到您 费尔柴尔德小姐
to meet you, Ms. Fairchild.
这是谁？
Who is this?
一位朋友
A friend.
如果我对你的看法是对的 玛格丽特
And if I'm right about you, Margaret,
如果我错了 你会知道的
you'd know if I wasn't.
不 我不...我不了解你
No, I don't... I don't know you
就像我不了解发生在我身上的事一样
any more than I know what's happening to me.
很少有人能像你一样把这件事做得这么好
Very few people could manage this as well as you.
-我管理不了 我真的管理不了 -那是谁？
-I'm not managing it. I'm not. -Who-who is that?
我害怕极了 我吓得魂飞魄散
I am frightened. I'm frightened out of my wits.
因为你只是旅途中的一个乘客
Because you're just a passenger on your way somewhere.
-让我们助您达成目标 -请帮帮我？
-Let us help you get there. -Help me how?
你是什么意思？
What do you mean?
-那是联邦调查局吗？ -嘘！
-Is that the FBI? -Shh!
我们希望为您提供保护
We want to offer you our protection.
我们直到看到你们
We held back on reaching out
的天气预报后才联系你们
until after we saw your weather report.
你有所保留吗？
You held back?
你是什么意思？那是什么意思？
What do you mean? What does that mean?
你需要律师吗？
Are you gonna need a lawyer?
873-2626是谁？
Who is 873-2626?
既然你知道这个号码
Since you know that number,
你一定已经知道它属于谁了
you must already know who it belongs to.
凯尔纳？
Kellner?
好的
All right.
仔细听
Listen carefully.
你不能回家
You cannot go home.
如果你心中有别的方向
If you have another direction in mind,
哪怕只是模糊的想法 也要去追随它
even a vague inclination, follow it.
如果我们能通过电话找到你 其他人就能
If we can find you by phone, others can
-在世界上找到你 -不 太晚了
-find you in the world. -No, it's too late.
他们...呃 他们已经找到我了
They... Uh, they already found me.
立即挂断电话 销毁你的手机
Hang up immediately. Destroy your phone.
你会如何找到我？
How will you find me?
我完全相信你会找到我们
I have every confidence you'll find us.
现在就做
Do it now.
等等 等等 你在干什么...你...你在干什么？！
Wait, wait. What are you... Wh-What are you doing?!
通过电话备份
Back up over the phone.
-什么？ -后退！
-What? -Back up!
-来吧 -好吧 我想指出的是 我在这里表现得
-Come on. -Okay, I'd like to point out that I'm being
非常冷静 而且我顺其自然
extremely cool here and that I'm rolling with it,
那可是部价值 600 美元的手机
and that was a $600 phone.
好吧 它仍然是一部价值 600 美元的手机 因为你错过了
Well, it's still a $600 phone 'cause you missed it.
杰克逊 向前拉 直到听到嘎吱声
Jackson, pull forward till you hear the crunch.
-来吧 -抱歉
-Come on. -Sorry.
我的天哪 你又错过了 我的天哪
Oh, my God, you missed it again. Oh, my God.
-好的 -什么？
-Okay. -What?
好的
Okay.
向前拉 走 走 走
Pull forward. Go, go, go.
继续前进 继续前进
Keep going. Keep going.
好的 好的
Okay. Okay.
-好的 我们走吧 我们走吧 -呃...这 这在哪儿？
-Okay, let's go. Let's go. -Uh... wh-where?
-北 -为什么？
-North. -Why?
因为丹尼尔·凯尔纳就在那里
Because that's where Daniel Kellner is.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
这个人是谁？他是你过去认识的
Who is this dude? Is he some guy from your past
-你从来没跟我提过的人吗？ -我不知道 杰克逊
-that you never told me about? -I don't know, Jackson.
-或者它是什么？ -你让我头疼
-Or what is it? -You're giving me a headache.
我不知道我在这里做什么
I don't know what I'm doing here.
我不知道他是谁
I don't know who he is.
我只知道他在北方的某个地方
I just know he's someplace north.
我只知道这些 好吗？
That's all I know, okay?
我的天哪 那是什么声音？
Oh, my God. What is that sound?
-你的冰雹 -哇
-Your hailstorm. -Wow.
天气摇摆？
Weather Shimmy?
开车就行了 开车就行了
Just drive. Just drive.
你抽到了 Kellner 号码是 2626
You got Kellner on 2626.
看看我刚刚发给你的视频
Look at the video I just sent you.
好的 稍等一下
Okay, hold on.
是啊 那又怎样？
Yeah. So?
她就是我们一直在等待的那个人
She's the one we've been waiting for.
她？为什么？
Her? Why?
你没听到她说话吗？
Did you not hear her?
是啊 我听到了
Yeah, I heard her.
你还在问为什么？
And you still ask why?
“不要害怕你不知道的事情”？
"Don't be afraid of what you don't know"?
她就说了这些？
That's all she had to say?
“不要害怕你不知道的事情”？
"Don't be afraid of what you don't know"?
她就是这么说的？
That's what she said?
你没听到吗？
You didn't hear it?
我们都听到了
We all heard it.
我们听不懂 这不是英语
We couldn't understand it. It's not English.
当然是英语
Of course it is.
我现在就在听
I'm listening to it right now.
我要把你送到她老家堪萨斯城去
I'm sending you to Kansas City, where she's from.
-我们会派车送你过去 今晚就走吧 -嘿 等等
-We'll get a car to you. Leave tonight. -Hey, wait.
-等一下 等一下 -不要在白天出行
-Wait a second. Wait a second. -Do not travel by day.
你没听到吗？这...这很清楚
You're not hearing it? It's-it's perfectly clear.
绕道经过收费站和收费公路
Detour past tollbooths and turnpikes.
嘿 听我说
Hey, listen to me.
你有没有放给其他人听过这首歌？
Have you played this to other people?
留在我身边
Stay with me.
车里会有汽车旅馆房间钥匙和路线说明
A motel room key will be in the car with directions.
圣地亚哥早上会来接你
Santiago will retrieve you in the morning.
到那时 我就会知道接下来会发生什么
By then, I'll know what comes next.
雨果 你吓死我了
Hugo, you're scaring the shit out of me.
丹尼尔 你有两个
There are two of you, Daniel.
一直以来都只有你们两个人
There's always been just the two of you.
你好 简
Hello, Jane.
请
Please.
请坐
Have a seat.
简 你现在在哪里？
Where are you right now, Jane?
您的位置在哪里？
What is your location?
-我不知道 -请放松
-I don't know. -Relax, please.
-你是谁？ -我来提问
-Who are you? -I'll ask the questions.
你还和丹尼尔·凯尔纳在一起吗？
Are you still with Daniel Kellner?
他在外面
He's outside.
你昨晚在哪里？
Where were you last night?
-血压高但保持稳定：156/94 -O2 下降到 96
-BP's high but holding: 156/94. -O2's decent at 96,
-但钠正在上升 -心率也很高...118
-but sodium's climbing. -Heart rate's hot, too-- 118.
-钾也处于临界值 -简！
-Potassium's borderline, too. -Jane!
-请稍候 Ringer's -简！
-Stand by, Ringer's. -Jane!
简！
Jane!
你昨晚在哪里？
Where were you last night?
黎明圣克莱尔修道院
Monastery of St. Clare of the Dawn.
圣克莱尔修道院？
Monastery St. Clare?
当然
Of course.
我记得我主日学校的圣克莱尔
I remember St. Clare from my Sunday school.
她病得太重 无法参加午夜弥撒
She was too sick to go to midnight Mass,
但她却看到了弥撒的幻象
and she had a vision of it instead.
她和我一样 同时出现在两个地方
She was in two places at once, like me.
圣克莱尔修道院 明白了
Monastery of St. Clare. Got it.
位于该地区东南13英里处
13 miles southeast of the District.
你离开的时候 是往哪个方向开的？
When you left, which way did you drive?
我不知道
I don't know.
太阳升起来了吗？
Was the sun up?
是
Yes.
你是开车撞上去的还是开离去的？
Did you drive into it or away from it?
它在右边
It was on the right.
我不喜欢你
I don't like you.
无需填写
Not required.
太阳在右边
Sun on the right.
太阳在右边...它们正向正北方向移动
Sun on the right-- they're headed due north,
可能向西北方向移动
possibly northwest.
可能在27号公路 18号公路或州际公路上
Could be on 27, 18 or the interstate.
州际公路不太可能
Interstate not likely.
重点关注辅路或县级公路
Focus on frontage roads or county highways.
你经过路牌了吗？
Did you pass a street sign?
是
Yes.
它说了什么？
What did it say?
“银泉：120 英里”
"Silver Spring: 120 miles."
路牌 “银泉：120 英里”
Street sign, "Silver Spring: 120 miles."
我离26号公路有六个城镇
I've got half a dozen towns off the 26.
银谷 橡树荫 铁湖 石山...
Silver Hollow, Oakshade, Ironmere, Stonemont...
简 请尝试了解更多详情
Try for more details, Jane.
你还通过了哪些考试？
What else did you pass?
一条河
A river.
过了一条河
Passed a river.
之后你看到城镇的标志了吗？
Did you see a sign for a town after that?
-是 -它说了什么？
-Yes. -What did it say?
赛克斯维尔
S-Sykesville.
-赛克斯维尔 -赛克斯维尔
-Sykesville. -Sykesville.
场变窄 跟踪并收敛
Field is narrowed. Track and converge.
查理27号 领跑 你还有四英里
Charlie 27, take the lead. You're four miles out.
保持最大合法速度
Maintain maximum legal speed.
看到标志后多久你转弯？
How soon after you saw the sign did you make a turn?
-几分钟 -几分钟
-A few minutes. -Few minutes.
你是向右转还是向左转？
Did you turn right or left?
-右 -右
-Right. -Right.
你还记得这条路的名字吗？
Do you remember the name of the road?
编号
No.
你还记得这条路吗？
Do you remember anything about the road?
那是一条土路
It was a dirt road.
土路
Dirt road.
Ash Hollow Road 三又四分之一英里
Ash Hollow Road, three and a quarter miles
Sykesville 外 死路
outside Sykesville, dead end.
尽头的农舍
Farmhouse at the end.
找到了
And found it.
灰谷路
Ash Hollow Road.
目标是一个农舍
Target is a farmhouse.
简 你做得很好
You've done very well, Jane.
为您的国家提供服务
A service to your country.
但我还有一件事要问你
But I have to ask you one more thing.
如果我们找不到丹尼尔 或者我们再次错过了他
If we can't find Daniel or we miss him again,
你可能需要亲自阻止他
you may need to stop him yourself
用尽一切办法
any way you can.
等等 BP 价格暴跌了 88 比 62
Hang on. BP just tanked. 88 on 62.
嗯 心率正在下降...降至 59
Uh, heart rate's dropping-- down to 59.
呃 O2是93 正在下降 91
Uh, O2 is 93 and falling. 91.
92 60 度 保持稳定 不过 氧气含量仍在下降
92 on 60 and holding. O2's still dropping, though.
开始打包
Let's start bagging.
确保气道畅通
Make sure you secure the airway.
80多度 继续
High 80s. Keep going.
快走开！
Get away!
简
Jane.
丹尼尔想做的是错的
What Daniel is trying to do is wrong.
这很危险
It's dangerous.
这将打破本已动荡不安的世界的平衡
It would tip the balance in an already destabilized world.
是
Yes.
简 如果需要的话 你能阻止他吗？
Jane, could you stop him if you had to?
否 否
No. No.
“父啊 你若愿意
"Father, if you be willing,
“让这杯离开我
"let this cup pass me by.
然而 不要照我的意思 只要照你的意思”
Yet not as I will, but as you will."
接下来基督说了什么？
And what did Christ say next?
“愿我的意志成就你的意志”
"By my will, thine will be done."
如果那一刻到来 我会陪在你身边
If the moment comes, I'll be with you,
简 你会行动起来
and you'll act, Jane,
出于对丹尼尔的爱 出于对人类的爱
out of love for Daniel, out of love for the human race.
现在环顾一下房间
Now look around the room.
慢慢地
Slowly.
从左到右
Left to right.
到此为止
Stop there.
起床
Get up.
走到柜台
Walk to the counter.
拿出菜刀
Pull out the chopping knife.
把你的手机给我！
Give me your phone!
-哦 糟糕！什么？ -把你的手机给我
-Oh, shit! What? -Give me your phone.
杰克逊 快点 快点 快点 把你的手机给我
Jackson, come on, come on, come on, give me your phone.
把你的手机给我 把你的手机给我
Give me your phone. Give me your phone.
-好的 等等 等等！ -加油！
-Okay, hold on, hold on! -Come on!
为什么？这样你就可以再把它扔出窗外了吗？
Why? So you can throw it out the window again?
嘿 雨果 为什么只有我一个人...
Hey, Hugo, why am I the only one...
-丹尼尔·凯尔纳 -哦 我的天哪 丹尼尔·凯尔纳
-Daniel Kellner. -Oh, my God, Daniel Kellner.
他们知道你在哪里
They know where you are.
他们知道 你明白吗？
They know. Do you understand?
这是谁？
Who is this?
不要回房子
Do not go back to the house.
Scan-Scanlon 为 Jane 做鸽子
Scan-Scanlon dove on Jane.
这对你来说意味着什么？
Does that mean anything to you?
-好的 把你的...给我 -看 他们找到你了
-Okay. Give me your... -Look, they found you.
我不知道你是谁 我也不知道他们是谁
I don't know who you are, and I don't know who they are,
但他们会杀了你
but they're gonna kill you.
-把手机给我 -他们会杀了你们两个
-Give me the phone. -They are gonna kill you both.
-把我的手机还给我！ -你需要离开
-Give me my phone! -You need to leave.
把手机还给我 玛吉！把手机还给我！我的天哪！
Give me my phone, Maggie! Give me my phone! Oh, my God!
我真是受够了你的那些疯狂事！
I'm so done with your crazy shit!
好的 好的
Okay. Okay.
好的
Okay.
我在做什么？我在做什么？
What am I doing? What am I doing?
我在做什么？我在做什么？好吧
What am I doing? What am I doing? Okay.
我在做什么？我在做什么？
What am I doing? What am I doing?
-我在做什么？我在做什么？ -等等！
-What am I doing? What am I doing? -Hold it!
-我在做什么？我在做什么？我在做什么？ -停止！
-What am I doing? What am I doing? What am I doing? -Stop!
-嘿！他在车里！ -小心 小心 小心！
-Hey! He's in the car! -Watch out, watch out, watch out!
我在做什么？
What am I doing?
射击轮胎！
Shoot the tires!
是他！是他！
It's him! It's him!
小心！
Watch out!
瞄准轮胎！
Go for the tires!
哦 糟糕
Oh, shit.
我在做什么？我在做什么？
What am I doing? What am I doing?
我在做什么？我在做什么？我在做什么...
What am I doing? What am I doing? What am I...
我在做什么？
What am I doing?
-举起手来！ -停止！
-Hands up! -Stop!
抓住他！
Get him!
滚出去！现在！
Get out! Now!
下车！
Get out of the car!
让我看看你们的手！举起手来！
Let me see your hands! Hands up!
举起手来！
Hands up!
系好安全带！
Get your seat belt on!
简！
Jane!
简
Jane.
-他癫痫发作了 把他拉开 -注意他的头部
-He's seizing. Stretch him out. -Watch his head.
-注意他的头部 -我需要一个咬合垫
-Watch his head. -I need a bite block.
趴下！
Get down!
哇 哇 哇 哇 哇！
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
不 不 不 不 不 不 不 不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不 不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no.
听着 简 不是你 不是你
Look, Jane, it wasn't you. It wasn't you.
是斯坎伦
It was Scanlon.
该设备 该设备
The device. The device.
掷骰子让他掷三 一 二 三 开始
Roll him on three. One, two, three, go.
刚才到底发生了什么？
What the hell just happened?
-保护设备！ -我明白了 我明白了
-Secure the device! -I got it. I got it.
我戴着手套 我戴着手套
I'm gloved. I'm gloved.
看看我们身后！告诉我你看到了什么！
Look behind us! Tell me what you see!
灰尘 我看到灰尘
Dust. I see dust.
他们来了！他们来了！
They're coming! They're coming!
停 停 停 停！
Stop, stop, stop, stop!
跑！
Run!
等等！
Wait!
-你在做什么？ -把它放到驱动器里！
-What are you doing? -Put it in drive!
-你看到他们了吗？ -你有画面感吗？
-You see them? -You got a visual?
-有人看到什么了吗？ -他们肯定过去了
-Anybody got eyes on anything? -They must have gone over.
请求水下搜索和打捞
Requesting underwater search and recovery
-现在就在现场 -他们倒下了 他们倒下了
-on site right now. -They're down. They're down.
他们倒下了 他们掉进水里了
They're down. They're in the water.
我们能派个小组下去看看能不能找到他们吗？
Can we get a team down there and see if we can find them?
-我们需要一些潜水员 -就在那里
-We need some divers. -Down there.
他们都认为世界正在走向毁灭
They all think the world's going to hell.
杰克逊 我得走了 好吗？
Got to get going now, Jackson, okay?
丹尼尔·凯尔纳会到场
Daniel Kellner's gonna be there.
现在还不行 但他很快就会来了
Not right now, but he will be soon.
-我们得往北走 -不不不不不不不不
-We got to go north. -No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
-现在必须往北走 -不 我们需要...
-Got to go north right now. -No, we need to...
-我们需要回医院 -不 不 不 杰克
-We need to go back to the hospital. -No, no, no, Jack.
这不是需要治疗的疾病 它不是...
This is not something you get treated for. It's not...
你知道你的问题是什么吗？
You know what's wrong with you,
那就是你认为我有问题
is that you think there's something wrong with me.
看着我 看着我
Look at me. Look at me.
如果我搬走 你会留下
If I moved, you'd stay.
-什么？ -堪萨斯城
-What? -Kansas City.
你想让我搬走 你却要留下
You want me to move. You're gonna stay.
你知道 现在发生的这件事 它...
You know, this thing that's happening, it's...
这不是我说的
It's not coming from me.
我感觉自己就像个乘客
It's like I'm just a passenger.
那不是件坏事
That's not a bad thing.
这真是一件好事
It's, like, a really good thing.
-就像你的音乐一样 -嗯哼
-It's like your music. -Uh-huh.
你知道自己进入心流状态的时候吗？
You know when you're in the flow?
感觉就像...
And it just feels...
我进入状态了
I'm in the flow.
好的
Okay.
我告诉过你 我会告诉你
And I told you I'd tell you
当我到达我应该去的地方时 而且...
when I get where I'm supposed to be, and...
就是这样
this is it.
-好的 -就在这里
-Okay. -Right here.
-这就是我应该在的地方 -好的
-It's where I'm supposed to be. -Okay.
所以...
S-So...
我们需要往北走 因为丹尼尔·凯尔纳在那里？
we need to go north because that's where Daniel Kellner is?
抱歉 不 他在东边
Sorry. No. He's east.
-哦 还有... -他现在在东部
-Oh. And... -He's east now.
你怎么知道它是东边？
How do you know that it's east?
只是 我隐约有这种感觉
It's just, I have this vague inclination.
但他现在在东边 他在东边的某个地方
But he's east now. He's somewhere east.
“某个地方”指的是哪里？
And where is "somewhere"?
你想让我开车吗？
You want me to drive?
我需要一杯水
I need a water.
嘿
Hey.
你好 嗨
Hello. Hi.
嗨 嗯...
Hi. Um...
你能帮我个忙吗？
Will you do me a favor?
科尔曼博士？
Dr. Coleman?
嗯 嗯 是的 是的 谢谢 谢谢您接听电话
Uh, uh, yes, yes. Thank you, thank you for taking the call.
呃 我不知道
Uh, I-I don't know.
她刚刚离开 是的 情况越来越糟 糟得多
She just took off, and y-y-yes, it's getting worse, much worse.
好的 谢谢
Yes, please. Thank you.
是的 稍等一秒
Yes. Hold on one second.
打扰一下 先生
Excuse me, sir.
你知道这附近的地址吗？
Do you know the address around here?
37 Pearl Street Decatur
37 Pearl Street, Decatur.
我们会在这里 谢谢
We'll be here. Thank you.
嘿 先生
Hey, mister.
她说要告诉你她爱你 但她要去东方
She said to say she loves you, but she's going east.
为什么选择堪萨斯城？
Why Kansas City?
最好集中精力确保你明天能到达目的地
Best to focus on getting you there tomorrow.
雨果 我是...
Hugo, I'm...
嗯 我想起来了
Uh, it's coming back to me.
事情正在慢慢恢复
Things are coming back to me.
什么东西？
What things?
动物
Animals.
友善又可怕的动物们看着我
Friendly, terrifying animals looking at me.
无论你多么努力 都无法移开视线？
And you can't look away no matter how hard you try?
不 不 他们得先把目光移开
No, no. They have to look away first.
这是回忆还是梦境？
Is this a memory or a dream?
我分辨不出来
I can't tell anymore.
丹尼尔？
Daniel?
丹尼尔
Daniel.
招募我并不是你的主意 对吧？
It wasn't your idea to recruit me, was it?
不仅仅是为了这个 而是为了WARDEX的最初目标
Not just for this but-but to WARDEX in the first place.
不 不是
No, it wasn't.
这其中是有原因的吗？
And there was a reason?
你想要我的具体原因是什么？
A specific reason why you wanted me?
除了你惊人的数字天赋之外？是的
Other than your prodigious gift for numbers? Yes.
你决定把这一切都藏在心里？
You decided to keep all of this to yourself?
因为我关心你
Because I care about you.
因为你还有工作要做
Because you have a job to do.
没有什么能阻挡这一切
And nothing can get in the way of that.
我的一部分...
There's parts of me...
从我小时候起 我就应该知道的事情
...from when I was a kid that I should be able to know,
但我却不知道
and I don't.
他们就这么走了
They're just gone.
我好害怕
I'm so scared.
你不需要这样
You don't need to be.
你拥有我和另一个人
You have me and someone else.
时机成熟时 一切都会明朗起来
And when the time is right, everything will become clear.
丹尼尔 你早上必须
Daniel, there's a place you'll need to be
准时到达一个地方
in the morning without fail.
明天将不再是另一天
There will be no other day like tomorrow.
你需要我去哪里？
Where do you need me to go?
KCXE？
KCXE?
KCXE是什么？
What's KCXE?
丹尼 我要请你做件事
Danny, I'm gonna ask you to do something.
我希望你先看一下这个
I want you first to look at this.
你听懂她说什么了吗？
Do you understand what she's saying?
我听到她说话了 这...这都是胡言乱语
I hear her. It-it's gibberish.
我看不懂
I can't understand it.
好吧 我刚听到这个
Okay, I-I just heard this for the first time,
我可以
and I can.
-这是英语 -英语？
-It's English. -English?
我的意思是 它是...它是我脑海中数学转换成的英语
I mean, it's-it's math turned English in my head,
翻译成文字
translated into words.
当我看到这个时 我听到这个
When I look at this, I hear this.
丹尼 我要请你做件事
Danny, I'm gonna ask you to do something.
你不能再信任我了
You can't trust me anymore.
抓到他了
Got him.
他们来了
They're here.
-他们来了 -什么？
-They're here. -What?
-走那一端 -加油 加油 加油
-Take that end. -Go, go, go.
-背包 背包！ -你先来
-The backpack. The backpack! -You first.
来吧
Come on.
这就是我全部的家当了
This is all I've got.
你会来 对吧？
You're coming, right?
糟糕
Shit.
突破！就在这里！
Breach! Here!
-不 拜托 拜托 拜托 -你必须接受这个
-No, come on, come on, come on. -You got to take this.
看在上帝的份上 简 别碰里面的东西
And for God's sake, Jane, don't touch what's inside.
走 走
Go. Go.
快离开那里！
Get out of there!
趴下！
Get on the ground!
它们被烧毁了
They're burned.
它不在这里
It's not here.
设备在哪里？
Where's the device?
丹尼尔 你被误导了
You've been misled, Daniel.
我们可以以后再谈谈这一切对我造成
We can talk another time about how hurtful
的伤害 但我们现在
all this has been to me,
就在这里
but here we are.
档案安全无虞
The archive's safe.
现在你要告诉我 WARDEX
And now you're going to tell me the name
中每个同盟军成员的名字
of every confederate at WARDEX
以及雨果的行动究竟计划着什么
and what exactly Hugo's operation is planning.
但首先 抛开这些废话...
But first, without all this nonsense...
你要告诉我你用这个设备做了什么
...you're going to tell me what you did with the device.
你到底在干什么？你这样开车？
The hell do you think you're doing driving like that?
你是特工托马斯·法利
You are Agent Thomas Farley.
您的十位ID代码为3893398887
Your ten-digit I.D. code is 3893398887.
今天的日期代码是什么？
What's the day code?
肯塔基小母马
Kentucky filly.
-格雷迪探员？ -是的 女士
-Agent Grady? -Yes, ma'am.
肯塔基小母马 斯坎伦先生派人来找我
Kentucky filly. Mr. Scanlon sent for me.
关注我
Follow me.
你就是她
You're her.
玛格丽特·费尔柴尔德
Margaret Fairchild.
乔斯林
Jocelyn.
离开她！
Leave her!
停止行动
Stand down.
我认识你
I know you.
我也认识你
I know you, too.
即将推出两款
There's two coming out.
不要让他们离开基地
Don't allow them off the base.
嘿 嘿 嘿 回来了
Hey. Hey. Hey, back inside.
我等了太久才告诉你
I've waited too long to tell you,
现在太晚了
and now it's too late.
但我爱你就像爱自己的儿子一样
But I loved you like my own son.
停 停 停
Stop. Stop. Stop.
他们说我们星期五可以去湖边
They said we could go up to the lake on Friday,
而且爷爷奶奶也会去
and-and Grandma and Grandpa will be there,
而且霍华德叔叔 鲍比 特蕾莎还有所有人
and-and Uncle Howard and Bobby and Teresa and everybody.
你是怎么认识这些人的？
How do you know these people?
我不
I don't.
你刚才还在和他们说话
You were just talking to them.
我不明白发生了什么事
I don't understand what's happening.
进来吧！
Just get in!
你看到了什么？
What did you see?
我的妻子
My wife.
我的天哪
My God.
她是什么？
What is she?
势不可挡
Unstoppable.
你要带我们去哪里？
Where are you taking us?
堪萨斯城
Kansas City.
为什么在那里？
Why there?
-我必须这样做 -你不必去...
-I have to. -You don't have to go so...
-是啊 嗯 是的 我愿意 -呃 你很享受这个
-Yeah, uh, yeah, I do. -Uh, you're enjoying this.
是啊 我的意思是 感觉很好 感觉很好 然后...
Yeah, I mean, it-it feels good. It feels good, and then...
是啊 但是...但是你知道的 你知道的
Yeah, but-but... but you know. You know.
我的意思是 你知道 你最近几天
I mean, you've been driving like a maniac
开车就像个疯子一样
the last few days, you know.
-你怎么知道的？ -我就是知道一些事情
-How do you know that? -I just know things.
只是 几天前我发生了一些事
It's just, something happened to me a couple of days ago,
现在我知道了一些事
and now I-I know things.
我不太想知道的事情
Things I don't really want to know,
以及所有我想知道的事情
and all the things I do want to know,
我其实完全不知道
I don't really know at all,
所以我只能顺其自然
so I've just been kind of rolling with it.
你知道 就像...哦 哇 你坐过牢？
You know, like... Oh, wow, you were in jail?
-那一定很... -嘿 嘿！
-That must have been so... -Hey, hey!
你明白我的意思吗？
You see what I mean?
太疯狂了 太疯狂了
It's crazy. It's crazy.
我看着某人 然后就直接上前拜访
I look at somebody, and I just drop in on them.
感觉就像 在那几秒钟里 我变成了他们
It's like, for a few seconds, I am them.
我看到了他们经历过的事情
I see the things that they've lived.
感觉这一切好像也发生在我身上一样
It's just like it's all happening to me, too.
你知道 就像...
You know, like-like...
就像现在你的肩膀疼得要命
like right now your shoulder's killing you.
是啊 你...你只想大喊
Yeah, and you-you just want to yell,
-“专心开车！” -专心开车！
-"Keep your eyes on the road!" -Keep your eyes on the road!
我知道 你无法停止想念简
I know, and you can't stop thinking about Jane,
简应该回到圣克莱尔修道院
and Jane should be back at the Monastery St. Clare.
-你说得完全正确 -简？
-You're absolutely right. -Jane?
但是昨天 我和杰克逊一起开车
But then yesterday, I'm driving with Jackson,
我闪了一下你的车灯 却没看到你
and I flashed on you without seeing you.
它太强了
It was so strong.
我直接就出现在你面前
I dropped right in on you
甚至都没看你一眼 而那是
without even needing to look at you, and that was
我第一次遇到这种疯狂的事情
the first time that crazy shit has ever happened to me.
你做这件事多久了？
How long you been able to do this?
从昨天开始
Since yesterday.
自从那只鸟
Since the bird.
-什么鸟？ -这只鸟
-What bird? -This-this bird.
从我的窗户飞进来
Flew in through my window.
它很漂亮 我看着它 然后它...
It was beautiful, I looked at it, and then it-it...
它是红雀吗？
Was it a cardinal?
我的天哪...怎么会...
Holy sh... How the...
你吓死我了
You're freaking me the fuck out.
我当时20岁 在上大学
I was 20. I was in college.
你基本上是要被淘汰了 对吧？
You were flunking out, basically, right?
是啊 我当时挺聪明的
Yeah, I-I was pretty smart.
你的确是 但那是因为聚会
You were, but it was the partying.
是派对和毒品
It was the partying and the drugs.
我的意思是 氯胺酮？拜托 老兄
I mean, ketamine? Come on, dude.
-请你停下来好吗？ -抱歉 我得停下来了
-Could you please stop? -Sorry. I'm stopping.
-我当时20岁 在上大学 -是的
-I was 20. I was in college. -Yes.
呃 当时天很黑 我躺在床上
Uh, it was dark, I-I was in bed,
我梦见有什么东西在看着我​​
and I dreamed that something was watching me.
我醒来时 看到这只鸟
I woke up, and there was this bird.
-那是一只红衣主教 -在窗户里
-It was a cardinal. -In the window,
它看着我 然后
and it-it looked at me, and after that,
一切都变了
everything just changed.
我看到了事物：背景 模式 人工制品
I saw things: context, patterns, artifacting.
我什么都看到了
I could see it all.
数组和条件语句突然出现在我的脑海里...
Arrays and conditionals just appeared in my head...
完全解决了 “如果 P 则 Q”
Fully solved. "If P, then Q."
没错 解方程
Exactly. Solved equations
-甚至不用思考... -你可以像读英文一样读八位二进制数据
-without even thinking... -And you could read
就像读英文一样
eight-bit binary data like it was English,
-就像读什么都一样 -是的
-like it was nothing. -Yeah.
你是怎么知道这一切的？
How do you know all this?
我不 你才有
I don't. You do.
上帝啊 你讨厌它
God, you hated it.
-那是一个诅咒 -是的
-It was a curse. -Yeah.
我无法与任何人产生共鸣
I couldn't relate to anybody.
我失去了所有的朋友 因为我无法忍受
I lost every friend I ever had because I-I couldn't stand
和人待在一起
to be around people.
直到你遇见简
Until you met Jane.
“不要害怕你不知道的事物”
"Don't be afraid of what you don't know."
-什么？ -你在电视上就是这么说的
-What? -That's what you said on TV.
他们说我在胡说八道
They said I was talking nonsense.
我听懂了每一个字
I understood every word.
我们怎么了？
What happened to us?
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
是谁？！
Who is it?!
博伊德 停下！
Boyd, stop!
博伊德！
Boyd!
糟糕
Shit.
我们得跳！我们得逃走！
We got to jump! We got to bail!
我做不到！我正在踩刹车！
I can't! I'm standing on the brakes!
我的天哪！我的天哪！
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
不不不不不不不不！
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
他正在后退！快离开！
He's backing up! Get out now!
好的 好的！
All right, all right!
快到梯子那里去！
Get to the ladder!
我的天哪 我的天哪
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
好的
Okay.
出发！跳！
Go! Jump!
你必须跳！
You got to jump!
跳！现在！
Jump! Now!
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
我无法呼吸 我无法呼吸
I can't breathe. I can't breathe.
我无法呼吸
I can't breathe.
-没关系 没关系 -我无法呼吸
-It's okay. It's okay. -I can't breathe.
-我觉得你正在经历恐慌症发作 -我的天哪
-I think you're having a panic attack. -Oh, my God.
-没关系 没关系 -我的天哪 我的天哪
-It's okay. It's okay. -Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
-没关系 我已经习惯了 -我的双手
-It's okay. I'm used to 'em. -My hands.
-我们没事 -就像我爸爸一样
-We're okay. -It's like my dad.
-就像我爸爸一样 我的手 -不 不 不 不 不 不 不
-It's like my dad. My hands. -No, no, no. No, no, no, no.
就像帕金森病一样 就像帕金森病一样
It's like Parkinson's. It's like Parkinson's.
这不是一回事 不是那样的
It's not the same thing. It's not that.
是的 是一样的
Yes, it is. It's the same.
不 他控制不了 我也控制不了
No, he couldn't control it. I can't control it.
-我无法控制它 -你可以
-I can't control it. -You can.
哦 我的天哪 我逃离了他
Oh, my God. I ran away from him.
-我不想再和他待在一起了 -不 不 不 停下
-I didn't want to be around him anymore. -No, no, no. Stop.
-我希望它消失！ -好的
-I want this gone! -Okay.
我只想让它消失！我只想让它消失！
I just want it gone! I want it gone!
我想摆脱它！我已经完全没有自己的想法了！
I want it gone! I just have no mind of my own anymore!
好了 停！停！别说话了！停
Okay, stop! Stop! Stop talking! Stop.
把你的手给我
Give me your hands.
-好吧 看着我 -不 不 不
-Okay, look at me. -No, no, no.
-看着我 -我会看到一些东西
-Look at me. -I-I'm gonna see things.
-我要去看一些东西 拜托 -好的
-I'm gonna see things. Please. -Okay.
用鼻子呼吸 用鼻子呼吸
Breathe through your nose. Breathe through your nose.
就这样 好的
That's it. Okay.
我感觉不到我的手了
I can't feel my hands.
好的 好的
Okay. Okay.
好了 把手给我 来吧
Okay, give me your hands. Come on.
来吧 把手放在那里
Come on. Put your hands there.
感觉到了吗？好 你感觉到了吗？
Feel that. Okay, you feel that?
我在这里 我在这里
I'm here. I'm here.
我们到了
We're here.
-我们没事 -好的
-We're okay. -Okay.
-我们没事 -我们没事
-We're okay. -We're okay.
我们没事
We're okay.
我们现在没事了 你也没事了
We're okay now. You're okay.
我们没事
We're okay.
好的
Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
凯尔纳从莱昂纳德山外的一个加油站打来电话
Kellner called in from a gas station outside Mount Leonard.
我将与圣地亚哥和他的船员见面
I'll meet Santiago and his crew.
我们几个小时后就能到
We can be there in a couple hours.
雨果？
H-Hugo?
请大家暂时离开准备区
Could everyone leave the staging area
一分钟好吗？
for a minute, please?
-现在 请！出去！ -好的 我们走吧
-Now, please! Out! -Yeah. Okay, let's go.
你好 雨果
Hello, Hugo.
诺亚 拜托了
Noah, please.
你带着那东西潜水真是大错特错
It's terribly misguided for you to dive with that thing.
这不是魔法棒
It's not a magic wand.
它不是武器 但它的功能
And it's not a weapon, but it has functions
远远超出了你有限的使用范围
very far beyond your limited use of it.
凯尔纳是个体验家 不是吗？
Kellner was an experiencer, wasn't he?
这就是我为什么不能扑向他的原因
That's why I couldn't dive on him.
是
Yes.
他是
He was.
In Vivo 17 让你去招募他？
And In Vivo 17 told you to recruit him?
你绝对无法理解
Not in any way you'd understand.
如果这就是他们的计划 雨果
If this is all their plan, Hugo,
你可以肯定 这符合他们的利益 而不是我们的利益
you can be sure it's in their interests, not ours.
这是一种非常孤独的世界观
That's a very lonely way to look at the world.
不 别对我摆架子
No, don't condescend to me.
我在听你说话 诺亚
I'm listening to you, Noah.
我对此了解颇多
Something I've learned quite a bit about.
来自你的朋友？
From your friends?
是
Yes.
他们认为同理心是一种进化优势
They regard empathy as an evolutionary advantage,
是最重要的进化优势
as the foremost evolutionary advantage,
事实上 是生命存在的核心
in fact, the core of animate existence.
我们拒绝这种理解
Our rejection of this understanding
正在将我们引向灭绝
is leading us to our extinction.
你帮助它逃跑是因为你那颗多愁善感的心吗？
And is your bleeding heart why you helped it escape?
五年前
Five years ago.
那是你 对吧？
That was you, wasn't it?
是
Yes.
撇开这种行为的疯狂不谈
The utter insanity of that act aside,
你怎么能骗我五年
how could you lie to me for five years
每次你走进门的时候都骗我？
every time you walked through the door?
你对我说的一切 都是转移话题
Everything you said to me, it was all diversion.
你究竟是什么时候失去方向感的？
When precisely did you lose your bearings?
大约在你丢失你的那一个的时候
Around the time you lost yours.
当你失去她的时候
When you lost her.
你失去了她 几乎立刻 你也失去了我
You lost her and almost immediately were lost to me.
因为你关机了
Because you shut down.
不要妄自了解我
Do not presume to know me.
当她去世时 你把所有人
When she died, you reduced everyone
都限制为需要知道的人 包括我
to need-to-know, including me.
因为你说得很清楚
Because you were very clear.
你只需要知道他们
All you needed to know was them,
而他们是不可知的 至少我们无法知晓
and they are not knowable, not by us.
他们会的
They will be.
In Vivo 17 是非人类
In Vivo 17 is nonhuman
但比你我更接近上帝 诺亚
but nearer to God, Noah, than you or I.
你不必害怕他们
You don't need to fear them.
我害怕我们
I fear us.
WARDEX存在的全部原因在于我们掌握的知识
The entire reason WARDEX exists is because of our knowledge,
我们确信人类无法接受我们所知道的
certain that the human race cannot accept what we know.
这个真相将颠覆全世界所有
That truth will upend all established order
既定的秩序
across the entire world.
凯尔纳偷走的档案是一种病毒
The archive Kellner stole is a virus
全世界对它没有任何免疫力
against which the world has zero immunity.
我花了35年时间保护...
I have spent 35 years protecting...
你自己的财富和权力...
Your own wealth and power--
你一直保护的只是这些
that's all you've been protecting.
诺亚 诺亚
Noah. Noah.
我们每个人都有一种基本的信仰需求
There is an essential need in all of us to believe
以及同样强烈的被信仰需求
and an equal need to be believed.
你违反了所有证据标准
You've violated every standard of evidence.
你把所有只想了解
You've infantilized anyone
自己所目睹之事的人都当成了孩子
who only wanted to understand what they've witnessed.
你残酷地压制了他们的提问
You've brutally stifled their questions,
大声斥责他们 嘲笑和羞辱他们
shouted them down, ridiculed and shamed
并压制他们 只因为他们
and overridden them for the crime
犯了“惊讶”的罪行
of simply being astonished.
我们相信信徒 然后剥夺世人
We believe the believers and then deny the world
相信他们的机会
the chance to believe them, too.
但人们不断好奇 不断遭遇未知
But people keep wondering, encountering the unknown,
将自己的经历告诉其他人
telling others of their experiences.
他们渴望真相
They are starved for the truth.
这场持续79年的恐怖运动
This 79-year terror campaign
充斥着混淆视听 谎言和掩盖真相 必须结束！
of obfuscation, lies and cover-up has to end!
我们准备向您进行演示
We're ready to show you a demonstration.
-出去！出去！ -对不起 先生 我们有...
-Get out! Get out! -Sorry, sir, we have...
转身离开！
Turn around and get out now!
找出昨天没来上班的12个人
Pull up the 12 who didn't show up to work yesterday.
我需要现在和他在一起的人的面孔
I need faces who are with him right now.
-她 -Grace Zhao 神经服务
-Her. -Grace Zhao, neuro-services.
-他 -内森·特温宁
-Him. -Nathan Twinning,
雨果的首席助手
Hugo's chief aide.
找到了进入他们移动运营商的后门
Got a back door into their mobile providers.
稍等
Hang on.
他们昨晚在这里关机了...
They shut down their phones last night... right here.
我会提前预测他们的路线 使之重叠
I'll project their routes ahead to overlap.
我可以提供方圆四分之一英里内的AI模型
I can give you the AI model within a quarter-mile radius.
莫拉修女 修女
Sister Maura. Sister.
简？
Jane?
简 你在哪里？
Where are you, Jane?
上帝爱我们吗？
Does God love us?
我不是问他是否爱我们？我知道他爱我们
I don't mean, does he love us? I know he does.
他只爱我们吗？
Does he love only us?
因为创世记说我们是他最伟大的创造
'Cause Genesis says that we're his supreme creation,
但是你认为有可能...
but do you think it's possible that...
在地球上
On Earth.
什么？
What?
创世纪
Genesis.
它说我们是上帝在地球上最伟大的创造
It says we are God's supreme creation on Earth.
你认为可能还有其他人吗？
Do you think there could be others?
是
Yes.
我也这么认为
I would think so.
他为何创造了如此浩瀚的宇宙
Why would he make such a vast universe,
却只为我们保留？
yet save it only for us?
如果你发现我们并非孤身一人 如果...
If you found out we weren't alone, if...
如果有人向你展示 向你证明...
if someone showed you, proved it to you...
那会吓到你吗？
...would that frighten you?
不 为什么？应该这样吗？
No. Why? Should it?
但如果这一切都崩溃了呢？
But what if it all collapsed?
为了你 也为了世界上每一位有信仰的人
For you and every other person of faith in the world.
然后呢？
Then what?
哦
Oh.
我亲爱的简
My dear, Jane.
我不认为你曾怀疑过你对上帝的信仰
I don't think that you ever doubted your belief in God.
我觉得你对人失去了信心
I think you lost your faith in people.
他们说你借了他们的手机 所以要你付钱？
They say you're paying because you borrowed their phone?
你在电脑附近吗？
Are you near the computer?
是
Yes.
KCXE是什么？
What is KCXE?
只有这些字母...KCXE
Just those letters-- KCXE.
还记得小时候吗？
Remember being a kid?
当然
Sure.
大部分是我十岁以后的东西
Mostly stuff after I was ten.
你能告诉我一些我小时候的事情吗？
Can you tell anything about me from when I was small?
它只是一只狐狸
It's just a fox.
不 不 不 不！
No, no, no. No!
-停！停！ -不 丹尼尔！
-Stop! Stop! -No. Daniel!
-走吧 跟我们走 -等等
-Let's go. Come with us. -Hold on.
-等等 -走吧
-Hold on. -Let's go.
我认识他 我认识他
I know him. I know him.
我们只是想快速检查一下你
We just got to check you real quick,
确保里面没有人和你在一起
make sure nobody's in there with you.
清除
Clear.
好的 开始装载
All right, let's load up.
你看 消防车就是这样...
See, the thing about fire trucks--
所有人都会赶紧给你让路
everyone gets the hell out of your way.
我就知道你会成功的
I knew you'd make it.
我很高兴你知道
I'm glad you knew.
毋庸置疑
Never a doubt.
玛格丽特
Margaret.
你好 玛格丽特
Hello, Margaret.
你知道我是谁吗？
Do you know who I am?
当然 你是雨果
Of course. You're Hugo.
内森
Nathan.
克洛伊·马利克
Chloe. Malik.
乔丹·莱蒂莎
Jordan. Letisha.
格蕾丝
Grace.
嗨 特里
Hi, Terri.
凯特琳 那是埃弗雷特
Kaitlyn. That's Everett.
我觉得我们基本做对了
I think we got it mostly right.
玛格丽特
Margaret.
你为什么不看我？
Why won't you look at me?
因为你就是...你就是那个人
Because you're-you're the guy.
你是无所不知的人
You're the guy who knows everything.
而我...我还没准备好知道所有的事情
And I'm... and I'm not ready to know everything.
包括 比如 为什么我爸妈的整个房子
Including, like, why-why my mom and dad's entire goddamn house
就这么摆在那里！
is just sitting right there!
发生了什么事？你为什么要这样做？
What is going on? Why are you doing this?
那是我长大的地方 那是我长大的地方
That's where I grew up. That's where I grew up.
这就是我的人生 这就是我的人生
This is my life. This is my life.
这很重要...我想要什么 我是谁
And this matters-- what I want, who I am,
不是作为你 他或她的身份 而是作为我自己的身份
not who I am as you or him or her, but as me.
不不不不不不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
否 否
No. No.
我不会成为任何人的宗教
I will not be anyone's religion.
我的房间
My room.
哦 我的房间
Oh, my room.
你为什么要建造这一切？
Why would you build all of this?
创建一段文字
To create a passage.
让您以最熟悉的
To return you to your experience
方式重返您的体验
in the most familiar way possible.
什么经验？
What experience?
你和玛格丽特分享的那一个
The one you shared with Margaret.
我分享过吗？
I shared?
我不会再回去了
I am not going back there.
-雨果 -你还记得那天晚上多少事吗？
-Hugo. -How much do you remember about that night?
我不记得了 我也不想记得
I don't remember, and I don't want to remember,
我也不想你让我记起
and I don't want you making me remember.
-好的 哦 我的天... -等等 等等
-Okay. Oh, my... -Wait. Wait.
等等
Wait.
1996​​年2月23日发生在你身上的所有事情
Everything that happened to you on the 23rd of February, 1996,
-都被屏蔽了 -我不想知道任何相关的事情
-is blocked. -I don't want to know anything about it.
要想知道接下来会发生什么
The only way for you to know what's next
唯一的办法就是了解之前发生了什么
is to understand what came before.
我不想谈这件事 真的不想 停 停 停
I don't want to talk about it. I don't. Stop, stop, stop.
然后你就会明白你的目标
And then you'll know your purpose.
请不要逼我 我不想听
Please don't make me. I don't want to hear it.
你将不再是乘客
You won't be a passenger anymore.
我告诉过你不行！
I told you no!
你有天赋 但没有控制力
You have the gift but no control.
不理解你的目的
No understanding of your purpose.
完全不知道你的处境
Not a clue as to what your situation
在今天之后会对你提出什么要求
will demand of you beyond today.
你获得它的唯一途径
The only way for you to acquire it
就是回到一切开始的地方
is to go back to where it all began.
回家
To go home.
玛格丽特 当你那样做的时候 你就会知道一切了
And when you do, Margaret, you'll know everything.
超越人类所能达到的极限
More than what was ever humanly possible.
他们给你们每个人都送了礼物
They gifted each of you.
玛格丽特 你一生中大部分时间里沉睡的东西
Margaret, what was dormant in you for most of your life
直到昨天才被激活
was activated only yesterday.
还有你 15年前
And yours, 15 years ago.
他们让你精通了
They gave you fluency in the language
宇宙之书所用的语言：
in which the book of the universe is written:
数学
mathematics.
教给你 灌输给你 让你能够理解他们
Taught it to you, imbued it so you could understand them.
他们赋予你理解我们的能力
And they imbued you so you could understand us.
就是你们两个
It's the two of you.
一直以来都只有你们两个人
It's always been just the two of you.
你可以引导它
You can direct it
或者感受它想带你去哪里
or feel where it wants to take you.
它可以找到你要找的东西
It can find what you're looking for.
它将成为你意志的工具
It'll be an instrument of your will.
但你必须全身心投入其中
But you must give yourself over to it.
我会弄清楚我身上到底发生了什么事
I'll find out what's happening to me.
什么？
What?
一切都会好起来的
It's gonna be okay.
我保证
I promise.
无论发生什么 丹尼尔
Whatever happens, Daniel,
-都不要放手 -别放手
-don't you let go. -Don't you let go.
玛格丽特
Margaret.
再环顾一下房间
Look around the room one more time.
你是一个十岁的小女孩 正在床上睡觉
You're a ten-year-old girl asleep in your bed.
是不是有什么事把你吵醒了？
Something woke you up, didn't it?
是
Yes.
所以你做了什么？
So what did you do?
我唱了我的歌
I sang my song.
♪ 前往他的城堡 ♪
♪ And away to his castle ♪
♪ 我们会去 ♪
♪ We'll go ♪
♪ 永远幸福快乐 ♪
♪ To be happy forever ♪
♪ 我知道 ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ 鸟儿会歌唱 ♪
♪ And the birds will sing. ♪
我能看到他们
I can see them.
就在那边
Right over there.
他们正走进房间
They're coming into the room.
不 不 不 不要和他们一起去
No, no, no, don't go with them.
它们不是动物
They're not animals.
不要跟他们走 他们不是动物
Don't go with them. They're not animals.
它们不是动物！
They're not animals!
-没关系 没关系 -他们不是
-It's okay. It's okay. -They're not.
它们以动物的形象出现 是为了安抚我们
They-they present as animals to calm us.
当我穿过玻璃时
When I walked through the glass,
就像一道温暖的水幕
it was like this curtain of warm water.
雪...
And the snow...
踩在脚上好暖和
was so warm on my feet.
房子
The house.
“汉塞尔与格蕾特”
"Hansel and Gretel."
嘘
Shh.
握住我的手
Hold my hand.
哇
Whoa.
你好 雨果
Hello, Hugo.
很高兴终于认识你
It's so nice to finally know you.
他们找到我们了
They found us.
它们是在前面还是后面？
Are they out front or out back?
很可能在各个方面
Most likely on all sides.
好的 把那个 呃...那个东西给我
Okay, give me the, uh... the-the-the thingy.
热成像显示此处有43个热源
Thermal imaging showed 43 heat signatures inside here.
这整个地区都是工业衰败区
This whole area's an industrial decay zone.
其他任何建筑物内都没有超过五个人
No other structure has more than five people in it.
嘿
Hey.
继续做下去
Get on with it.
谁都别动
No one move.
谁都别出声
No one make a sound.
他们看不到我们
They can't see us.
给我
Give it to me.
这不对
This is not right.
他们看不到我们 但他们能看到这个
They can't see us, but they can see this.
我们现在必须行动
We need to move now.
这不会持续太久 我们现在就得走了
This is not gonna last long. We got to go right now.
看 他们看不到我
Look. They can't see me.
他们看不见我们 我们走吧
They can't see us. Let's go.
安静 安静
Quiet, quiet.
从后门进去 任何后门都可以
Through the back doors. Any back door.
安静点 安静点 沿着小巷走
Go quiet. Go quiet. Down the alley.
-走吧 走吧 -安静
-Let's go. Let's go. -Quiet.
所有人 停止移动
Everybody, stop moving.
看那里 看那里
There. Look there.
哦 天哪 我要疯了
Oh, God, I'm losing it.
我快崩溃了 你得开快点
I'm losing it. You need to go faster.
-快去消防车 -我坚持不住了
-Get to the fire truck. -I can't hold on.
-我坚持不住了... -我们得走了
-I can't hold... -We got to go.
保持灯光亮着
Stay on the light.
我坚持不住了
I can't hold on.
走吧
Let's go.
那里 那里 保持点亮
There. There. Stay on the light.
-保持灯光亮着 -光！光！
-Stay on the light. -The light! The light!
坚持住 抓住什么东西
Hang on. Grab ahold of something.
我们该听哪一个？！
Which one do we follow?!
她只有一个去处
There's only one place she's going.
欧盟各地正在
Urgent measures are being
实施紧急措施
implemented across the European Union,
在已启动申根法的地区
where the Schengen Code has been invoked,
关闭所有国家边界...
closing all national borders...
-我... -我知道 我知道
-I... -I know. I know.
即将遭受导弹袭击
...for an imminent inbound missile attack.
在朝鲜 第二个分裂派别
In North Korea, a second breakaway faction
宣布已控制
has announced it has taken control
多达四个军事基地
of as many as four military bases
并确认从平壤部署部队
and confirm troop rollouts from Pyongyang.
克莱在哪里？
Where's Clay?
BBC的
Taran Davies at the BBC
塔兰·戴维斯在朝鲜中央通讯社内部有联系人
has a contact inside the Korean Central News Agency,
他早些时候说过
the official news agency of the North Korean government,
这样的话...
and had this to say earlier...
你在这里做什么？
What are you doing here?
你应该在医院
You should be in the hospital.
什么...
What...
邓肯真是个好孩子
Duncan is such a good boy,
他明天需要你陪在他身边 即使他自己说不出来
and he needs you there tomorrow, even if he can't say it.
我要到主播台上进行直播
I'm going on air at the anchor desk
播报特别报道
to deliver a special report.
O...好的
O... o-okay.
好的
Okay.
我该如何到达控制室？
How do I get to the control room?
我需要去装卸货码头
I need to get to the loading dock.
这是丹尼尔 这是雨果
This is Daniel. This is Hugo.
-Clay 你能帮帮我们吗？ -当然
-Clay, can you help us? -Of course.
呃 我不知道发生了什么事 但是拜托
Uh, I don't know what's happening, but come on.
海莉
Hailey.
装卸货平台是右边第二个标志
The loading dock is the second sign to the right.
到底发生了什么？
What exactly is happening?
怎么了？
What's up?
玛格丽特将接管主播台
Margaret's taking over the anchor desk.
-什么？ -帮助她
-What? -Help her.
-好的 -控制室
-Okay. -The control room.
我为什么要这么做？拜托
Why am I doing this? Come on.
控制室在楼上 跟我来
The control room's upstairs. Just follow me.
我报警举报了他
I called the police about him.
我和玛丽亚搬出去了 我们现在和我姐姐住在一起
Maria and I moved out. We're with my sister now.
-她很好 -好
-She's good. -Good.
-谢谢 -当然
-Thank you. -Of course.
你想化妆吗？
Do you want makeup?
是的
Yeah.
下面发生了什么事？我不得不切到广告
What's going on down there? I had to hard-cut to commercial.
-特别报道 -什么报告？
-Special report. -What report?
-这人是谁？ -他要上传了
-Who's this guy? -He's gonna upload.
照他说的做
Do exactly what he says.
我直接把它放在你的服务器上
I'm putting it directly on your server.
-这是你的咖啡吗？ -是的
-This your coffee? -Yes.
播放在哪里？
Where's playback?
-呃 那是我 -请稍候 内容有点多
-Uh, that's me. -Stand by. It's kind of a lot.
TD 你们的播放频道是什么？
TD, what are your playback channels?
它们分别位于 W X Y 和 Z 轴
They're in W, X, Y and Z.
我们要把它们全部装上车
We're gonna load up all of them.
它是生的 所以你需要自己搅拌
It's coming in raw, so you got to mix it.
而且 嘿 没有磁带延迟 我的意思是 一帧都没有
And, hey, no tape delay. I mean, not a frame.
直接进入信息流并保持打开状态
Go straight to the feed and leave it open.
导演 无剪辑
Director, no cuts.
这段视频会自动播放
This plays itself.
它很快就会超出你的市场范围
It's gonna go outside your market fast.
如何从联盟服务器路由
How do I route from the affiliate server
以便网络可以访问？
so network has access?
你真觉得电视台会为了你手里的东西而放弃
You really think network's gonna bump World War III
《第三次世界大战》吗？
for whatever you got?
当然会
You bet they will.
-嘿 Shea -是的
-Hey, Shea. -Yeah.
呃 你能跳起来吗？
Uh, can you hop up?
-什么？ -克莱普尔说玛格丽特将去
-What? -Claypool said that Margaret's
做一个特别报道 所以...
gonna go on for a special report, so...
谢伊 从椅子上起来
Get out of the chair, Shea.
-谢谢 -是啊 当然
-Thanks. -Yeah, sure.
你换发型了吗？
Did you change your hair?
嗯 算是吧
Uh, kinda.
-嗯 你好 -你好
-Um, hi. -Hi.
你好吗？你过得怎么样？
How are you? How are you doing?
太棒了
Great.
两队人马 找到电源
Two teams, find the power source
和应急发电机 并将它们关闭
and the emergency generator, and shut them down.
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
阿尔法小队 你们和我一起去那个变电站
Alpha Team, you're with me on that substation.
过了中央大道两个街区
Two blocks past Central Avenue.
-太棒了！太棒了 团队！ -开始吧！
-Bravo! Bravo Team! -Let's do it!
Bravo 跟我一起！
Bravo, with me!
我们正在寻找这栋楼后面
We're looking for a backup generator
的备用发电机
in the back of this building.
出发！
Let's go!
好的
Okay.
一切就绪
Good to go.
设置
Set.
待命
Stand by.
应急发电机将在五秒内启动
Emergency generator kicks in in five seconds.
三号摄像机待命
Stand by, camera three.
我们要直接跳到法院的镜头
We are gonna go right to that shot of the courthouse.
丹尼尔 他们在外面 我们...我们现在得走了
Daniel, they're outside. We-we need to go now.
我们现在必须走了
We need to go right now.
百分之百 一切就绪
Hundred percent, good to go.
-玛格丽特 你明白我的意思吗？ -我能听到你说话 库珀 是的
-Margaret, you got me? -I can hear you, Cooper. Yeah.
-我们还有十分钟直播 -好的 谢谢
-We're live in ten. -Okay. Thank you.
等等！
Wait!
五 四...
Five, four...
它们就在那里
There they are.
关闭它们
Shut 'em down.
三 二...
...three, two...
哇！
Whoa!
不要看她的眼睛
Don't look her in the eyes.
让她起来
Just get her up.
等等！
Wait!
-拉它！ -简
-Pull it! -Jane.
-停！停！ -告诉他们真相
-Stop! Stop! -Tell them the truth.
回到这里
Get back here.
哇 哇 哇 哇！
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
我们已恢复在线
We're back online.
你难道不打算阻止她吗？
Aren't you gonna stop her?
你难道不打算阻止她吗？！
Aren't you gonna stop her?!
好的 库珀
Okay, Cooper.
必须有人告诉纽约 让他们看到这一点
Somebody has to tell New York so they can see this.
拿起电话
Pick up the phone.
给他们打电话 这件事不能只局限于本地
Call them. This can't stay local.
务必让他们知道
Make sure they know.
纽约控制
New York control.
这是堪萨斯城 KCXE 4 电视台的台长
This is the director of KCXE 4 Kansas City.
我们需要您立即查看我们在 Skypath 上的信息流
We need you to take a look at our feed on Skypath right away.
嗯 好的
Uh, yeah. Okay.
呃 给我预览一下堪萨斯城的比赛画面
Uh, give me Kansas City feed on preview.
安静！安静！闭嘴！
Quiet! Quiet! Shut up!
快看！闭嘴！
Take a look! Shut up!
看看预览内容
Take a look at what's on preview.
这是谁？我们为什么在看这位女士？
Who is this? Why are we looking at this lady?
擦拭至三
Wipe to three.
晚上好
Good evening.
我是玛格丽特·费尔柴尔德 为您带来特别报道
I'm Margaret Fairchild with a special report.
自 1973 年以来 一个名为 WARDEX 的非政府组织
Since 1973, a nongovernmental organization known as WARDEX
一直在收集和压制已知的
has collected and repressed known instances
外星人造访我们星球的事件
of extraterrestrial visitation to our planet.
此外 WARDEX与国防部合作
Further, in collaboration with the Department of Defense,
没收 逆向工程
WARDEX has confiscated, reverse engineered
并制造了基于回收残骸的技术
and manufactured technology based on recovered debris,
在某些情况下 他们还
and in some cases, they have engaged
审讯和虐待
in the interrogation and mistreatment
非人类居住者
of the nonhuman occupants.
昨天 我与一群勇敢的人会面
Yesterday, I met with a group of courageous people
他们直到最近还在努力掩盖真相
who until recently had worked to hide the truth.
但真相属于你
But the truth belongs to you.
这是给你的
This is for you.
这是我们所有人都能看到和知道的
This is for all of us to see and to know.
今天是信息披露日
This is disclosure day.
Viper-1 统计未知联系人
Viper-1, tally unknown contact
at 2-7-0 angels 2-5
at 2-7-0 angels 2-5.
Viper-2 投放点 他们到底去哪儿了？
Viper-2, drop-off. Where the hell did they go?
没有应答 没有三模式
No squawk, no mode three.
极速加速 正中靶心 1-3-5-41
Extreme acceleration, bull's-eye 1-3-5-41.
锁定坐标
Locking coordinates.
联系人分为两部分
Contacts divided in two.
现在有七个了 哗啦哗啦
There's seven of them now. Splash, splash.
水下保持超音速
Holding supersonic underwater.
等等 你当面告诉她 这件事我来处理
Wait, you tell her live. I'll deal with this.
把堪萨斯城的那个人给我找来
Get me the Kansas City guy.
-我会和他谈谈 -顶线
-I'll talk to him. -Top line.
你是谁？这些东西你是从哪里弄来的？
Who is this? Where did you get this stuff?
肯定是美国空军
Definitely says U.S. Air Force.
-我到底在看什么？ -我们是否验证过此信息源？
-What the hell am I looking at? -Did we verify this feed?
这是假的吗？这是人工智能吗？
Is it fake? Is it AI?
鉴别器说不
Discriminator says no.
这些是真实像素
These are ground-truth pixels.
等等 我们怎么知道它是真的？
Hang on. How do we know it's legit?
欧洲仍处于高度戒备状态
Europe remains on high alert
整个欧洲大陆 申根法...
across the entire continent, where the Schengen Code...
你是谁？这些东西你是从哪儿弄来的？
Who are you? Where'd you get this stuff?
在美国
In the United States,
军事战备级别已达到自1962年古巴导弹危机
the military readiness level is at its highest designation
以来的最高水平...
since the Cuban Missile Crisis in 1962...
-妮可 把堪萨斯城贴到墙上 -等等 等等 等等
-Nicole, get Kansas City up on the wall. -Wait, wait, wait.
我们需要找个人到现场
We got to get somebody on the ground
-来核实这件事 -不 没有时间了
-who can verify this. -No, there isn't any time.
我们需要进入编程领域
We need to break into programming.
-我做不到 -丽贝卡必须...
-I can't do that. -Rebecca has to...
我不会走完九个步骤
I'm not going through nine steps.
有人会把它拉出来
Somebody's gonna pull it.
我们得转变思路 跟她好好谈谈
We got to pivot. Get in her ear.
-你确定吗？ -现在！走 走！
-Are you sure? -Now! Go, go!
提示器响起 我们有新的文案要发布了
Cue the prompter. We got new copy coming.
-请查看您的预览监视器 -新副本
-Take a look at your preview monitor. -New copy.
我们即将从朝鲜话题转向另一个故事
We are about to pivot from North Korea to another story.
嗯 抱歉
Um, sorry.
我们刚刚获得了一项非凡的进展
We have just been handed an extraordinary development.
我这里有一条“突发”消息要告诉你
I've got a "breaking" banner for you.
上面写的是什么？
What does it say?
她在堪萨斯城说的话
The thing she said in Kansas City.
发送出去
Send it out.
收到 明白了吗？
Copy that. You got that?
呃 我们暂时中断报道
Uh, we're interrupting our coverage
切换到我们在堪萨斯城的附属机构
to switch to our affiliate in Kansas City.
KCXE 刚刚获得了档案影像
KCXE has just obtained and is now releasing archival footage,
机密图片和视频
classified images and video that until this moment
据称这些内容此前一直受到政府的限制
are claimed to have been under government restriction.
我们正在尝试进行身份验证
We are attempting to authenticate now,
但是...好吧 我可以告诉你的是...
but... okay, what I can tell you is...
-Kit 你看到这个了吗？ -哦 女孩 我看到了
-Kit, do you see this? -Oh, girl, I see it.
它在 EchoStar 12 上 转发器 10 Ku 数字
It's on EchoStar 12, transponder ten, Ku digital.
-拿走它 -你在做什么？
-Take it. -What are you doing?
通过泳池推送发送出去
Sending it out on the pool feed.
KCXE 堪萨斯城 这里是 Kit NBC 纽约控制中心
KCXE Kansas City, this is Kit, NBC New York control.
什么？你不能这么做 这是NBC独家报道
What? You can't do that. This is an NBC exclusive.
-不再是了 -伙计们 我们是不是把病毒传染给他们了？
-Not anymore. -Are we giving them the bug, guys?
-否 否 -好的 好的 酷 酷 酷 酷
-No. No. -All right, okay, cool, cool, cool, cool.
我得做一次干净的喂食 我明白了
I got to do a clean feed. I got it.
CNN 这里是Kit NBC纽约控制中心
CNN, this is Kit, NBC New York control.
30 RS 30 拿30 走
30. RS 30. Take 30. Go.
这是一条中断信息 ABC 这里是Kit
This is an interrupt. ABC, this is Kit,
-NBC纽约控制中心 -这是我们所有人都能看到的
-NBC New York control. -This is for all of us to see.
-EchoStar 12 转发器十 -RS 22. 22 拿
-EchoStar 12, transponder ten. -RS 22. 22, take.
BBC 这里是Kit
BBC, this is Kit,
-NBC纽约控制中心 -今天是信息披露日
-NBC New York control. -This is disclosure day.
-RS 35 拿35 -Pool feed 这里是NBC纽约
-RS 35. Take 35. -Pool feed, this is NBC New York.
您可以前往 EchoStar 12
You can go to EchoStar 12,
-转发器十 -拿 还有36
-transponder ten. -Take. And 36.
-走第36步 走 -这是一个中断
-Take 36. Go. -This is an interrupt.
70年
...70 years.
是的 那是美国海军...
Yeah, that is a U.S. Navy...
这是美国海军的录像 来自某处的机翼摄像头...
This is U.S. Navy footage, a wing camera somewhere over...
据报道 其中一些片段源自
Some of these clips reportedly originated
安全的军事设施
from secure military installations.
我们和你们一样 都是第一次看到这个
We are seeing this for the first time along with you.
在那里你可以看到类似军事录像的内容
There you can see what looks like military footage.
我的天哪 它来自新墨西哥州的罗斯威尔
My goodness, it's from Roswell, New Mexico.
传闻已久的罗斯威尔坠毁事件发生在1947年...
The long-rumored Roswell crash that would've been in 1947...
据说可能是1947年7月8日
I'm told possibly July 8, 1947.
-回滚 Y 取 Y -我可以看到一片碎片区
-Roll back Y. Take Y. -I can see a debris field.
等等 有个日期
Wait, there's a date.
上面写着1947年7月7日
It says July 7, 1947.
呃...
Uh...
我们不是...
we're not...
是啊 我不确定这是什么
Yeah, I'm not sure what this is.
我不知道是否...
I don't know if...
对不起 我...
I'm sorry, I...
我不知道该说什么 嗯...
I do not know what to say about this. Um...
好吧 我很抱歉现在要你和我
Okay, I'm so sorry that you're having to watch this
一起看这个
along with me right now.
尚不清楚这是否是
It is unclear if this is
官方政府披露...
an official government disclosure...
-并取X -或者如果它已经
-And take X. -...or if it has been leaked
非官方地泄露给我们
to us unofficially.
或者这完全是其他的东西
Or if this is something else entirely.
哦 我的天...嘿 控制中心 这是要直播吗？
Oh, my... Hey, control, is this going out live?
有人看到这个吗？
Are people seeing this?
你现在看到的是这个
You are seeing this.
好的 我们...
Okay, we are...
我们也看到了这一点
we are seeing this, too.
我现在被告知这是大量资料的一部分
I'm now being told this is part of a trove of material
这些资料可能已经获准公开发布 也可能尚未获准公开发布
that may or may not have been cleared for public release.
34. RS 34 拿走
34. RS 34, take.
在那里你可以看到它是一个...物体
There you can see it's a... object.
呃...
Uh...
呃 我们...呃...
uh, we... uh...
我的天哪
My God.
还有更多精彩内容即将到来
There's a lot more coming.
拿
Take.
这是1965年的宾夕法尼亚州凯克斯堡
It's Kecksburg, Pennsylvania, 1965.
这显然是另一个有军方人员的坠机地点
It's apparently another crash site with military.
呃 有一个...
Uh, there's a...
平民似乎负责
civilian who appears to be in charge.
我的天哪 这太不可思议了
My God, this is extraordinary.
好的 让我把话说清楚
Okay, let me be clear.
这不是现场直播画面
This is not live footage.
这些是以前被列为机密的录音
These are previously classified recordings,
直到最近一个小时才解密
declassified only within the last hour.
今晚的国际危机已经接近难以想象
Tonight's international crisis was already
的程度 但现在这已经是不可想象的了
approaching the unimaginable, but this is now inconceivable.
我们似乎是...
We appear to be...
见证长期以来秘而不宣
...witnessing the public release
的资料公之于众：
of material long shrouded in secrecy:
引发深刻问题的影像资料 关于我们天空
footage that raises profound questions
中正在发生的事情
about what is happening in our skies,
关于我们是谁的本质 以及我们
what is the nature of who we are
的位置...我很抱歉
and what our place is... I'm sorry.
38. 第38卷
38. Roll 38.
我们承诺与您同在
We promise to stay with you
只报道我们能够核实的事情
to report only what we can verify,
但我们不再谈论未经证实的报道
but we are no longer talking about unconfirmed reports.
世界已经发生了翻天覆地的变化
The world has just changed profoundly.
如果你正在观看此视频 如果你看到了此视频...
If you are watching this, if you are seeing this...
你并不孤单
...you are not alone.
慢慢地
Slowly.
-是的 然后当你得到... -不 我是说 在...
-Yes, and then when you get... -No, I'm saying, on...
听
Listen.